Greetings, my little Kerbalites and Kerbalnaughts.
Yes, Catnip, it is I, your father.
And I'm here to lay down the law.
Today, we're reaching for the stars.
And I will take no less.
What's going on, huh?
Happy freaking Saturday, man!
Are you guys excited?
Let me hear what your plans are before we get started here.
I need to take a room measurement here.
How's it going?
You got big plans?
On this wonderful weekend?
The weather is amazing here in Europe.
Land on Kerbal.
You mean Kerbin?
I don't know what Kerbal is.
Reaching the star?
Okay, I like it.
Just sleeping?
Two days of relaxation.
Nice.
I can get behind that.
Meeting up with friends later.
Great!
Kerbal is the star.
Oh!
That's so weird, though, KushCut, because in the map view of the game, or in the, you know, whatever, it's Cold Sun.
So what's up with that?
That's weird.
Coding a game right now?
Nice.
Good luck with that.
Just gonna chill and do absolutely nothing.
And you know what, Quasant?
It's gonna be everything you ever hoped for.
Your streams make me so happy?
Thank you for saying that.
I appreciate it.
I'm glad you like them.
You're gonna get your life together for the preparation of new semester.
Man, come on.
You know that's not gonna happen.
You keep saying that.
Everyone says that every time there's a new semester.
And then it's the same shit.
And then a new semester, you say the same thing.
But, I think you can be the exception.
I believe in you.
Big hug from Italy.
Big hug back from Denmark.
Is it hot down there?
Should I study for physics or watch the whole stream?
You should study for physics.
Definitely.
It's easy to give out advice.
It's harder to follow it.
But I'm gonna give you the advice.
Go study.
Close the stream.
You will be the exception.
I'm glad to hear it.
You got diagnosed with ADHD and got the funny medication too.
Okay.
Well, congrats, I guess.
I mean, not congrats on your ADHD, but congrats on getting, you know, diagnosed with it at least.
And getting something for it.
Advanced linear algebra exam in a week.
You got this, Omar.
Man, I remember that one being a tough one for me.
Linear algebra, man.
That's been ages.
Holy shit.
How old was I at that point?
Maybe like 20.
God damn, that's 14 years ago.
Wow.
Whew.
Thoughts about free IVA?
I did install it and try it.
I didn't like it, man.
I didn't go for it.
I quickly tried it out, you know, real quick.
I put in a little capsule with a guy.
Didn't like it, man.
Felt hella janky.
Didn't like it.
I also tried, or not tried, but I looked up the IVA stuff, you know, to make the insights more complicated or whatever.
So you can control things.
I didn't like that either, man.
It didn't fit the game, in my opinion.
But that's just me.
You know?
Like, it didn't really fit the whimsical nature of the game in a weird way.
If there was like a middle ground, you know, where it wasn't as crazy complicated and realistic looking, maybe I would have gone for that, you know?
What about you, Oliver?
Any plans this weekend?
Well, I already did hang out with someone yesterday.
Honestly, no plans.
I'm gonna stream today.
I'm gonna stream tomorrow as well, probably.
Minecraft.
And other than that...
Maybe I'll start working on a thumbnail for something.
Nah, just a friend.
Use 100 potatoes to highlight your message.
Wait, what?
What did you say?
I missed someone.
Dominique.
Long time VOD watcher.
Finally, my schedule lined up to be able to watch live.
What's the new dark mode UI mod from last time?
It looks way better than the previous one, but I couldn't find anywhere what's the new mod.
It's something that I had made with AI.
It's just the Opus 5.5 personal mod.
That's really all it is.
I just installed it via that.
It's a crazy time we live in, man.
It's pretty much just a reskin to make it look darker to not be like flashbang.
It's just that I didn't really like the sea theme icons and the style.
It looked a little too modern and...
I don't know, sci-fi-ish.
But that's fine.
Modded Minecraft and KSP playthroughs right now.
I never knew life could be so peak.
Just you wait, wobble tiger!
I actually...
Guys.
I installed something crazy.
I installed a crazy visual mod.
It's not perfect... yet.
But it's looking amazing, okay?
I'm not gonna say what it is.
I'm not even gonna react to it when it happens.
In fact, I'm gonna be completely stone-faced, or whatever you call it.
And I'll let you guys try and figure out what it is I've added.
Okay?
It's gonna be pretty obvious.
I wish you would release all these vibed mods.
The thing is though, people...
I don't really wanna distribute mods made this way because people don't like it.
You know?
I'd rather just keep it for personal stuff.
I mean, I'm, you know, vibing these fucking mods and I'm having a blast with it.
I'm just enjoying it, you know?
I don't wanna, you know, become a target in some way.
Because there's like a brigade against this stuff, you know?
I'm just having a blast with it, man.
Maybe I'll do it, at some point.
Just put a disclaimer in the description.
Yeah, I guess I could do that.
Dude, it's a crazy time we live in that you can do this stuff, you know?
I love it, man.
This is like the golden age of modding right now.
Holy shit.
Barrier to entry is like non-existent.
My mom could do it.
It's awesome.
The parachute mod looks amazing.
It was a little buggy last time.
It's fixed now.
It shouldn't bug out anymore.
It was like weirdly...
You know, spassing out or whatever.
It's gone now.
That's fixed.
So it's even better now.
Fuck yeah.
Now I'm not gonna put it behind a pay thing.
No way.
I already cringed a little bit when I had to download that cloud mod behind the pay wall.
Like, what the fuck, man.
But I did it anyway because it looked awesome.
I mean, I...
I had to do it, right?
It looked amazing.
Nah, I wouldn't really say it's the same, Krigo.
It's just me playing the game, right?
Also, some of the mods, I guess, contain some stuff from the game itself.
So distributing it would technically not be allowed, I guess.
You don't want to distribute any actual game files when you upload a mod.
As far as I'm aware, right?
It would have to be like only files that adjust whatever's already in the game that you own.
So yeah.
Although you could probably change it so that it would do it that way.
G-game, it's applying a tint, yes.
It's like a filter.
But there are some icons and stuff where you can't just do that.
Because you have to sort of...
Like, for example, some of the icons or so are like dark or black in the default UI.
And you have to sort of invert that part only to be like brighter, right?
Otherwise, you can't read it if you darken everything.
So it's like a combination.
Guys!
Are you ready for some Kerbal Space Program?
I don't even know what I'm gonna do today.
Oh!
Last time I unlocked some new shit.
Apparently we can now do flight planning.
I'm so excited for that.
I've yet to touch it, obviously.
So we're gonna experiment that.
Figure out how it works.
And...
What am I even gonna do, man?
Ah...
I guess I'm gonna try and land on Minmors today.
That's like the next big step.
And apparently you can also take...
Surface samples?
I don't remember whether or not I unlocked that.
But I wanna unlock that.
Obviously we're gonna go for a lot of science.
And...
Just keep unlocking things, man.
Going to orbit and...
Maybe we'll try some kind of...
Docking...
But I guess we need docking items for that.
Or...
You know, parts.
We'll figure it out.
Also...
It's so sad Valentina is dead, man.
Both Jebediah and Valentina have laid down their lives for this program.
It is such a shame.
I will say though, Valentina's death was epic.
There's no cooler way to go than that, right?
Meanwhile, Jebediah died for Clampatron.
Fuck.
That's terrible!
Oh my god, I'm so excited.
Cheers.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Oh wait, I need to...
Transition some music.
Oh yeah.
Well...
And...
Oh, I timed the clap perfectly!
Did you see that?
Unbelievable.
Wow.
I never do that, man.
I don't think I've ever actually hit it that precisely before.
That was amazing.
Hmm.
Okay.
So, we have half a million in the bank.
82.8 signs.
That's really nice.
That means we can soon unlock something new in here.
I don't even know what I want.
Oh wait, I wanted this one.
Stack separator.
I don't know what the difference is between that and...
You know, the other ones.
Is it these ones?
The decoubler.
Maybe it's like a more powerful version or...
Something.
Duh.
Oh god.
This song right here is so good.
It's like promising...
Crazy adventures ahead in a way, you know?
I love it.
Monopropellant tanks.
Uh, we need to see mission control though.
We have three contracts!
Holy shit!
Oh, bring the moonstone back.
I still haven't found that.
Science data from space around Minmus.
That one should be easy.
In fact, I can't believe I haven't done that.
Didn't I go around Minmus last time?
Unless I got this after.
Probably did.
Explore Minmus.
We gotta orbit it.
Go on an orbital spacewalk.
Okay.
And return to Kerbin.
Guys, we're doing that!
Unless there's more.
Umm...
There's nothing else with Minmus.
Actually, that's plant flag.
I mean, we can go try and land on Minmus.
Actually, that's not a bad idea.
I'm taking that too.
We can have seven contracts now.
Nothing else I want.
Oh, maybe science data from space around Kerbin?
That one should be pretty easy.
The thing is though, I feel like I've already gotten all the science I can from this.
You know?
Unless it counts when you just pick up zero science.
I don't know.
You know?
Like, I made a report.
It's not a worthwhile report, but I did it.
It's in the bag.
I don't know.
I mean, we can try.
Umm...
Yeah, okay.
Let's try it.
We'll see.
Umm...
Maybe it's time to start hiring pilots, by the way.
Right now we have Carson.
Who has two stars!
Radial normal attitude hold.
What's the difference between that and...
Oh, he's actually the only pilot.
Umm...
I think we need another pilot here.
It's gotta be Cargill.
Haha, what a name.
Cargill Kerman.
I like that they're all just related.
That's funny.
Does it cost anything?
Oh!
It cost like 50!
It didn't say!
Oh!
Oh wait, it says here.
Oh my god, that's expensive!
The next one is gonna be 140?
We cannot lose any Kerbals!
This is not great.
Apparently she's very stupid.
Look!
The stupid meter is off the charts.
And again, I'd say Bill is the stupidest one.
Ah, alright then.
Then we have this stuff.
Maybe I should look into this.
Takes reputation and gives science.
Wait, what do I don't need?
Or what do I not want?
Takes funds and gives me more science?
I feel like I don't want any of this.
Is that crazy?
Uh, well, let's make a rocket to go to Minmus!
We're gonna land on Minmus and we're gonna get the science around...
Uh, the space there.
And we're gonna orbit it and we're gonna do all the things.
We also have this now.
Lander can.
Maybe that's what we need for this.
You know what?
Let's go for it.
Not even that...
Oh, we can only have one in here.
Hmm.
Wait, what is the point of this?
Can I even come back with this thing?
Oh, we have this one now!
Right, but it's bigger.
Uh, maybe we need to do this.
I kinda wanna do a big one.
Parachute.
Then we need these guys.
Uh, X.
Yes.
This is gonna be, uh, Minmus Lander.
We're not gonna name it yet.
But soon.
Wait, didn't I get a...
1.87.
Is that the one?
Oh, man!
Sweet.
Now we need to separate.
Beautiful.
What then?
I guess we want...
Dude, I have to remember, this is like, big now.
The other part was, I don't know, half the size.
So this is gonna change things a little bit.
I think it's this one.
Yeah.
But do I want that one?
Oh, that's way too big.
Oh my goodness.
Um...
Yeah, just go for that one.
Do I like that?
No, I don't.
I like the white one.
And then we need a...
Ah, but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The problem is, I tried this once.
It didn't work.
Cause we need legs.
And the engines are too big, right?
That's why I didn't do this.
Yeah, there's no way.
Look at how big that is.
The poodle.
I mean, that's way too big.
Oh my god.
Uh, I'm okay, okay.
I guess we don't need...
Okay, scratch this.
Scratch it.
Let's look at what we have.
I'm just gonna take something we have already.
Maybe Minmus Maximus.
Let me see that.
Hey, I like that!
That's good design right there.
And we're gonna...
We have this one.
We have that one.
This one's gonna be left behind.
And this is just a standard, isn't it?
Yeah, standard setup for science.
Love it.
And...
What else?
We got a big booster.
These two...
Separate...
Parachutes.
The problem is though...
We gotta land, right?
Hmm.
Wait, where's the engine?
Oh.
Ah...
Wait a sec.
Hmm.
Okay, check it out.
I have an idea.
What if we do something really dumb?
Um...
Structural...
What's that?
Launch Stability Enhancer.
I mean...
What's preventing me from...
Just doing something like this, you know?
Maybe we do like four of them?
Maybe even adjust it a bit?
Wait, what?
Hmm...
I mean, obviously this is not gonna be aerodynamic.
It's horrible.
I actually hate it.
Okay.
Minmus...
Maximus is not a good idea.
Let's try something else.
Uh...
Don't save.
What did I use to go to the moon?
Probably the moon lander.
Oh, is it moon or white boy, maybe?
No, it's this one.
Oh, it's ugly as hell!
Uh...
We gotta fix this.
This is ugly.
Nah, bro.
There's no way.
I mean, wait a sec.
Why didn't I use this part up here?
Can't we do something like this?
Ah, that's why.
Cause it was...
Yeah, I remember now why I did all this.
I'm going through the same...
Freakin' thought processes here.
I mean, we...
Okay, listen.
This will work probably.
The thing is though, it's ugly.
I don't like when it's ugly.
Maybe this is like a silly thing.
Or a silly hill to die on, but...
I like it to be kinda nice looking, you know?
What else we got?
The moon or white boy?
What is that one?
That's also a landing platform.
But I feel like we can connect this better.
Right?
God, it's ugly.
What have I made?
Wait, I have an idea.
Start over.
New.
Don't save.
What if...
We take this?
I just need to test something real quick.
This one is not as...
Okay, it is kinda long here.
Shit.
Okay, fine.
Whatever.
I'll take the moon lander.
I mean, it's not that ugly, you know?
Okay, it's kinda ugly.
Um...
Oh, wait.
Wait.
Are there batteries in here?
That's what we need.
That's kind of a big deal now.
Ooh, there's not.
Holy shit.
I have learned my lesson.
There we go.
Battery.
Sorry.
Maybe I'll do two...
Oh, wait.
Isn't there like a limit?
On thingies?
Parts.
Yeah, we can only have 30 parts.
That's the limit.
Right.
But that's fine.
I mean, we can do it with this.
Retract it.
Da-dum-bum.
What do I have in here?
Is that a swivel?
It is indeed.
I like this rocket.
What can I say?
I like it.
It's not the prettiest rocket, but it's mine.
I will say, though...
Maybe we do add a bit of science...
to this.
This one.
You know?
It's a bit of a tall boy.
But surely it'll be okay.
Haha.
So, we do that one.
These two.
Kinda wanna separate that.
For more control.
And then these two.
Who's gonna fly it?
Carson?
You know what?
What if we take Cargill?
Or Cargel.
Cargel.
That's probably not how you pronounce that.
I'm gonna say...
Cargill.
Cargill is good.
I mean, it's not that ugly.
I actually think it's kinda pretty.
This will now be...
Minmus...
Explorer.
Because we're gonna do a bunch of things.
We're gonna do...
A bunch of things.
That's what I said.
Save it.
Okay!
I think we're ready.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's...
Go.
Whew.
Cargill.
Let's see what you've got.
Alright, here we go.
You ready?
Taken off.
Beautiful.
It's a beautiful day.
For some rocketry.
I'm gonna start turning at 2500.
Oh wait, I can't turn yet.
I'm doing my best.
I'm turning as much as I can.
It feels like I'm turning more than I am, but I'm not.
Why does my rocket wanna go north?
Or sorry, south.
Time for staging.
There we go, baby.
I'm gonna turn even more.
I'm gonna keep it at like 45-ish.
That's about 45.
Rotate.
Roll program.
Oh, I need to see this.
Oh, we're already at 80, what the fuck?
Go horizontal then.
There's my part.
I think we can stop now.
And wait until we're at the top.
God, this thing is ugly looking.
It really is.
How long?
1 minute 30?
We're probably gonna be at around 1000, so it's gonna take...
I don't know.
A minute, I think, to burn.
So we're gonna do like 30 seconds.
Go faster.
I think we start burning now.
Oh, wait, shit.
Oh, miscalculated!
Oh, it's gonna...
Oh, this is bad.
Look at this fat boy.
Uh-oh.
This is gonna take...
50 years.
But hey, we have a lot of fuel.
Look at this.
Actually, maybe it's fine.
We haven't even crossed the...
Apoapsis yet.
I'm gonna keep it horizontal here.
Dude, I don't know if we're gonna have...
We gotta go to Minmus.
We need to land.
And we gotta come back.
I don't know if we can do that.
This is...
I mean...
The moon's a different story, you know?
But...
Minmus...
Okay, we're at 1800 now.
Oh my god, it's taking forever.
At least we're not in the atmosphere.
We're still kinda high up here.
In fact, I'm gonna angle it a little bit more like this.
Is that a good idea?
Maybe it's not a good idea.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know!
I'm looking at my Apoapsis.
And...
Oh god, it's taking forever.
Actually, this is fine.
Oh my god, it's horrible.
Guys, we fucked it up already.
Shit, we gotta keep burning.
Periapsis.
Oh no.
Okay, I mean...
We're in orbit!
This was terrible!
Hey, it was the first launch of the day, okay?
Caught me some slack here.
Alright.
So now...
We wanna go...
To Minmus!
And let me just confirm here.
So we have...
Fuck the Moonstone.
Transmit...
From space around Kerbin.
Okay, so...
I guess we can do that on the way home.
Plant flag on Minmus.
That one's...
A given, I guess.
Recover science from around Minmus.
And orbit.
Okay, okay.
Basically, we just gotta land, cause everything else comes automatically.
Uh, so wait.
Okay, so hold on.
We unlocked something new.
I need to see this.
What was it?
Oh god.
Was it that one?
Uh, this one.
Selected on the map.
Set as target.
We wanna do that anyway.
Oh!
Oh, look at this now.
Yeah, that's what we unlocked.
Graphical Maneuver Editor.
Oh wait, these are the same symbols as here.
Wait, I don't understand.
Oh wait, I'm changing things.
No, wait.
Um...
Oh, I can warp there, look!
I can be like, oh, I wanna go to here?
Maneuver?
That's cool.
Wait.
I feel, I feel like an idiot.
Give me a second.
Uh, oh, we can play this, I guess.
Uh...
When a Maneuver node is selected on the map, or by interacting with its selection...
Display buttons...
The Precision Maneuver Edit panel...
Right, so this one.
Post Maneuver Orbit Information displays in the Orbit Information panel.
Delete selected...
Oh wait, I didn't see this.
What?
Maneuver.
Wait, where's that button?
Wait, what?!
I'm confused.
Instructions on using...
Yeah, okay.
Maneuver Handles.
Use the handles to adjust maneuver direction by click, drag, or scroll.
The center buttons adjust the time of the maneuver in the same way.
Scale Slider.
Shows the current rate of change applied when using the handles.
Increase or decrease the time of the maneuver by one orbit.
Okay, so we can definitely, like, plan...
Some sort of burn, right?
That's the whole point.
Numeric inputs.
Oh, I can say, like, I want 80 meters in pro grade.
Wait, um...
Make, like, one here.
Oh, that's cool.
It's kinda like the same thing when you...
Uh, if you're on a collision course with another body's sphere of influence.
Then you get to preview what your orbit's gonna look like.
Oh, and that moves it...
Around that way.
Orbit.
Oh, I'm changing the time?
Oh, it's on the next go-around, I guess.
Cause you can't go back.
Oh, the scale is here.
Ah, okay.
I see.
Oh man, that's actually really cool.
Oh my god.
Okay, so wait, I'm here now.
We haven't done any burning yet.
This is just, like, planning.
This is flight planning.
I wonder if you can do this on the ground.
Maybe you can, like, input what your orbit's gonna be, and then start doing this before you even launch.
So you can plan every stage of the flight, you know what I mean?
Haha, look at that!
Whoa!
Escape.
It's basically like simulating a burn, you know?
Okay.
Well, um...
I guess what we wanna do...
So, it's gonna be, like, here.
So we put one here.
So that's gonna be in 32 minutes.
And we burn prograde.
Oh wait, that's the moon.
Oh!
Aha!
We actually have an encounter with the moon here on the return trip.
Because we're gonna spend a lot of time out here.
And by the time we come back, the moon is already gonna be here.
That's funny.
But we wanna go further.
Tar- wait, target position at closest approach.
Okay, so we're not actually in the sphere of influence here.
But we can move it.
Wait.
I can also just do this.
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait!
It's tilted!
Right!
Hold on, we actually gotta fix that first.
Wait, unless I just...
If we wanna burn this way, we just burn like that, right?
Wait, what the fuck?
How do I, um...
Can I, like, see the difference in inclination, I wonder?
Oh!
Angle between Minmus Explorer and Minmus!
That's it right there, phase angle.
But is that...
I think that's right now.
It's not actually for the maneuver node?
Is it?
Yeah, it's right now.
Okay, shit.
Oh no, wait, it says maneuver one.
Wait, what?
This is... I feel like this is confusing.
I feel like it would be easier not even to use this.
But that's probably wrong.
Haha.
I mean, obviously you wanna use this, but...
It doesn't look like the phase angle is...
Oh!
Wait, it's the...
Oh, okay, I see what it is.
I see the problem.
We actually have to...
So, imagine...
You have a flat disc.
You know?
In your hands.
And if you then tip that disc over, there's a line along that disc.
Well, I guess it could be this one, I guess.
You know, where...
This line is not gonna change.
Right?
So, you wanna burn along these.
So, we actually wanna burn right here.
And since we are...
Let me see.
We're coming this way around.
We gotta burn down.
So, this way.
Wait, let me look at the...
Wait, what?
Why is it...
Why is it saying 113?
113?
I'm so confused.
This...
I feel like this one is lying to me.
Cause if you look at the angle from...
Like, visually.
It looks...
Like...
3 degrees.
Or something.
Look, I can even unline it by eye here.
Right...
There...
Ish.
Why is that...
Wait, I'm so confused.
Is it because of this?
Target?
Oh!
Look!
Now we see it!
Oh!
Okay.
It's because we had...
Uh...
Orbit.
But we wanna be relative to the target.
It's just funny that it's said.
Angle between Minmus Explorer and Minmus.
You know?
That's weird.
So wait.
How does this work?
So how do I...
Wait, there's something I actually don't understand here.
How do I do it then?
Wait, hold on.
Uh, this one.
The Precision Maneuver Edit Panel.
Okay, so we've done this.
Oh, there's an arrow.
Maybe that's it.
Oh, is that it?
Wait, it's just gonna tell me?
Burn time, 14 seconds!
Node in 12 minutes?
Oh wait, I guess we don't want orbit.
We want...
Why are these not available?
Is that because...
Oh, it's because we are not actually going to have, like, an encounter.
Not yet.
Right now, we're just fixing inclinations, so we're on the same plane.
And then we can start worrying about, you know, getting out there.
Also, I keep looking at the moon and thinking that's where I'm going, but it's not.
We're going to Minmus.
Um...
So wait, I need to see this again.
Target.
So we're...
Ah, but wait a sec!
This is my current...
Uh, phase angle.
It's not the phase angle for the...
Maneuver node.
I wonder how I can...
Display that.
Advanced orbital info.
Argument of periapsis.
Wait, where did my...
Oh wait, I have to click here.
See, now it's saying this again.
Even though I have it on target.
Wait, what?
I am so confused.
So we have currently input minus 177 meters per second in the...
I don't know what this is called.
Normal, I guess?
Normal to the velocity.
I wish this...
Like, I don't understand that.
Okay, whatever.
Fast forward.
So basically we start burning at 14.
It's gonna take out all the calculation here.
I mean, mental calculation, you know?
Intuitive calculation.
16...
15...
14...
Burning.
Aha!
Look at this!
Oh, that's actually kinda sick.
Okay, get ready to stop.
Stop.
That's beautiful, dude.
Wow.
Precision maneuver.
So now...
Now that we have the right inclination, now we just go for it.
How the hell did I hit that last time?
I didn't do this last time.
I guess it was just sort of, uh...
We were aligned in such a way.
Oh yeah!
So...
I think Minmus was like there last time.
And I burned like...
75-ish degrees or so to here.
Where we happened to have the same sort of...
You know, where these two, uh...
Conics would intersect, so to speak.
Um...
Like, if you have two discs, you know, they intersect over there.
So now I basically wanna...
Aim for like...
Here.
So that would mean like there.
And we just burn Prograde.
Oh god.
I keep losing the handle here.
Oh, look at that!
We can even move it around like this.
God, the camera angle is like...
This is gonna be...
Pain in the ass when we get further out, man.
So wait, I need to understand these lines.
Which one am I?
The moon encounter?
Oh, so the green one is the one I'm on now.
Oh wait, that's the moon!
Oh wait, I'm an idiot!
Fuck!
We're going for Minmus!
There!
I mean, look at that!
Intuition was on point, man.
Much easier.
So here we're gonna have encounter there.
Oh, that's actually beautiful.
Maybe we can even adjust this...
Um...
Oh, that's why you have this, I guess.
Let me put the scale down.
Whoa!
That's sensitive.
Oh my god.
All the way down.
Well, I guess I can just click on it.
Two million meters!
Oh wait, wrong way.
Maybe it's also like this?
Minmus is...
Okay, Minmus encounter is there.
Hmm.
It's gotta be like a way to...
Focus view?
No.
I need to focus on this.
But hey, you can do this at least.
At least.
Cannot auto-warp so far.
How do I return?
Oh, I didn't open my cheat sheet.
Fuck.
I mean, we're fine.
We're gonna have an encounter.
But we haven't burned yet.
Uh...
Node in T-7 minutes.
Burning for 56 seconds!
How do I actually go back?
Let me just click somewhere.
Oh, I can probably unfocus?
No.
Oh my god, dude.
I'm losing my mind.
Okay, guys.
I'm actually gonna ask you guys.
How do I fucking unfocus right now?
How do I unfocus and go back to the view I had before?
Rotund, tell me.
There's like four different answers.
Double click, curve it.
Okay, hold on.
That's a good idea.
Let me try.
Thank you!
Okay, good.
Oh, I guess I can just do that then.
Ah!
That's kinda nice.
It is...
It is still...
Janky feeling.
Honestly.
Okay.
So now...
Um...
Node in 6 minutes.
Slim Shady, you're on.
Wait.
So we're here.
I feel like it's more complicated with the fucking maneuvering thing.
I kinda just wanna burn, you know?
I don't wanna...
Plan.
I just wanna go.
Wait, let me just double check.
We are actually going to Minmos.
Okay, we are.
It's not the moon.
And it does look like we're sort of...
This I don't understand.
Like...
What?
Oh, wait a minute!
Phase angle!
I know what it is!
It's the angle in the orbit between...
I guess...
How is it counting that?
I guess it must be...
Yeah.
It's not actually between, like, inclinations.
Hmm.
Okay.
I see.
Let's just go here and...
Do the burn.
And I guess it's just gonna tell us again.
So...
I've spent all my time in map view.
Haha.
I mean, look at this random ass spot on the nav ball here.
Trust the nav computer.
Ba-da-la-da-da-da-la.
Wait, why is it that way?
Oh, it's because...
When we reach...
This point here, that will probably be exactly on our vector anyway.
Watch.
Yeah, look!
It's gonna coincide.
Of course.
Okay, so we gotta start burning in...
At 56 seconds.
And I guess it's not exactly on top, because...
Wait, where am I?
Wait, maybe I should focus this instead.
I can't.
Oh my god, never mind.
Uh, oh shit!
I forgot to burn!
Burn!
Here we go.
I love that it's gonna...
Like, it just tells me here.
Here we go, let's see if it's correct.
Wait, how are we not at the node yet?
I guess we're gonna be approximately here?
When we're done...
Burning, then.
I feel like this is too early of a burn.
I feel like...
I should've burned later on this.
Yeah, we're not gonna be all the way over here.
Oh god.
I...
I don't understand what's happening.
Which...
Wait, which one is...
I'm so confused.
What the fuck?
Wait, the...
Stop that.
Maybe it didn't burn enough?
Hold on.
Oh wait, I didn't burn enough?
Dude, I like...
I like doing it manually!
I feel like it's more precise.
It sounds crazy, but...
Maybe we just need to learn how to do it.
There we go.
See?
That works.
Boom.
I don't know why this is...
Flashing like that.
But wait, are we gonna...
Crash into it?
Dude, we don't have a lot of fuel!
This is...
Okay, we're just gonna go into orbit and come back.
We're not gonna land.
There's no way we have enough.
Ah, shit.
Okay.
Well, we are on our way.
3,300 meters per second.
That's quite fast.
Cargill!
Are you excited?
Yes.
Good!
We're gonna need your excitement.
Speed up!
Oh my god, it's so pretty!
Look at that marble.
Bye-bye.
I'm going to the sour candy moon.
Let's see if we can find it now.
That's the moon.
Is it that one?!
I think I see it!
Yeah, look!
We even had it.
Why won't it...
Oh, there we go.
Minmush!
Look!
Speed up.
Oh, it's coming.
We're coming.
Gonna take a while, because we're moving slower and slower.
Let me speed up even more.
Whoa!
It feels like we're approaching super fast, but we're definitely not, right?
Oh, I can see it spinning.
Whee!
Okay, slow down, slow down.
Let's see the map.
I wish it would just focus on my vessel at all times.
Okay, we're actually super close.
Uh, wait.
Focus, Minmush.
There we go.
Let's see.
What's that?
Oh, Minmush escaped.
Okay.
Here we come.
This is gonna align with that.
Boom.
Let's get into orbit, shall we?
But we're gonna wait until, uh, periapsis.
The angle is awkward.
Well, that's okay.
Gonna speed up here.
That looks about right, doesn't it?
Right there.
Let's see it.
Hoi!
Here we go, baby!
Oh, look!
I don't have the, uh...
Prograde stuff, because...
Cargill isn't very experienced yet.
So cool.
Uh, let's not do target.
We're gonna do...
Orbit now.
There we go.
You ready?
You ready, kids?
Oh, we have to burn a lot here.
Whoa!
That's cool!
Yeah, there's no way we can land.
I mean, look at our fuel, dude.
I mean, you know what?
I'm happy with an orbit, and we can even do something funky here.
When I get to, uh...
The periapsis, I'm gonna burn...
Retro again.
Just so we can get a little closer, too.
Ah, but wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We can't waste fuel, dude.
We are here, let's do the science.
And then after that, we get out, man.
We are here.
We're here.
So now...
Material study.
I may have done this already when I was here last time.
Yeah, only 8.2.
The high radiation environment caused a few of the samples to glow.
It looks like it would be fun to paint the rocket with this.
Really?
Doesn't seem very fun, does it?
Wait, battery!
Ah, we have plenty!
138, dude?
Oh, no problem.
I probably should turn off SAS.
Just to, you know, be safe.
Pressure data.
Oh my, we're not even getting anything.
What the fu- Brother!
What?
Maybe I burn and get even closer to the moon then.
We use a little more.
Guys, we're gonna use a little more.
Angle the ship.
Okay, you ready?
Orbital info.
50 kilometers periapsis.
We're gonna be very close.
Actually, it's not even that close.
Holy shit, man.
This thing is small.
That blows my mind.
There we go.
We're gonna...
Sit right past it at...
Frickin' Mach.
Holy shit, you know?
Okay.
Let's wait.
Dude, we are moving at 14...
Wait, how long is this gonna take?
I feel like this is gonna take forever.
Am I crazy?
Look at the time warp!
It's been seven days already.
Seven days since launch.
I'm so sorry, Cargill.
I threw you into the deep end!
On your first mission.
This is a crazy first mission though.
Wow, look at that.
What is that?
That looks kinda shiny.
Looks like ice, actually.
Man, that is eerie.
Maybe I go EVA.
Actually, wait, let me try science here.
Crew report.
High over Minmus.
Still nothing.
But surely we're gonna be low over Minmus.
Soon, right?
I kinda wanna burn more.
But maybe I shouldn't.
I'm gonna burn more.
We're gonna burn a little retrograde here.
Obviously, it's not ideal.
We wanted to do that at...
Apoapsis.
So this is gonna be a little less efficient.
Fuck it, man.
Fuck it.
22...
16...
Dude, 13 kilometers only?!
Come on, that's gotta be like...
Move a little closer.
Remember, we also gotta get back to...
Kerbin.
God, what is this gonna look like?
Holy shit.
Wow.
Imagine...
One...
Frickin'...
Little space rock...
Crashing into...
This machine right here, and you are dead.
That is terrifying.
Okay.
Bye-bye, son.
An EVA.
EVA report.
Just above Minmus' Midlands!
Oh my god!
19.2 science!
The mesmerizing aquamarine flats almost make you forget to keep one hand on the ship's handle at all times.
Yeah, we are very close.
Let's do more.
Because now it's time for science!
Mystery goo.
Oh, we gotta be inside for this.
Okay, okay, that's no problem.
Mystery goo, let's see what it does.
24 science!
Oh my god!
Give it to me.
And we have...
Barometer...
28!
Wow!
Thermometer is gonna give us 19!
Minmus is cold!
Ice cream is cold!
Coincidence?
You hope not!
Huh?
If my grandmother was a...
Or had wheels, she would have been a bike!
I love that one.
I'm gonna reset this.
We're gonna do it again.
What do we get?
Oh!
It's 60!
Holy shit!
The high radiation environment caused a few of the samples to glow.
I love it.
I wanna eat the samples.
I'm gonna transfer the data.
Put it in there.
Actually, I'm gonna transfer everything.
Everything gets transferred.
Transfer that guy.
Can we transfer...
Crew report?
Oh, this is actually...
Wait, wait!
We need to EVA report.
EVA report.
Activate a light.
Yes.
Um...
EVA report.
You are craving mint ice cream right about now.
Dude, that actually sounds pretty fire.
I would love some of that.
I prefer pistachio, though.
Pistachio ice cream superiority.
You know?
Oh my god.
We gotta go spacewalk a little bit, though.
Whee!
Yes.
Oh yeah!
We also have this now.
First person.
Now we can get some really nice views.
Turn off the UI.
Ooh!
Look at that!
It's so dark here, though.
You can barely see anything.
I feel like we should have done this on the bright side.
Oh my god.
Okay, let's go.
Whee!
It's a little hard to control.
Get back.
Grab.
In.
Okay!
So now we got all the science.
This one is pretty much dead weight now.
This is gonna be discarded at some point.
We should close this.
And...
How do we get home, man?
Let's see this.
Oh my...
Dude, we may not have enough.
This is gonna be...
Actually, hold on.
It's not actually that bad.
Minmus is, like, tiny, you know?
Almost no gravity.
So escaping this is gonna be...
Easy peasy.
In fact, I'm just gonna burn at periapsis.
What are you gonna do about it?
Right there.
We're gonna turn...
Uh...
Retrograde.
Which is over here.
This is gonna be very tight, by the way.
You ready?
Wait!
I'm burning retro!
Fuck!
It's the other way!
Shit!
Oh no!
I wasted!
I wasted fuel!
No!
Undo it!
Hup!
Yeah, that's not a great orbit.
Me no likey.
Aw, shit!
Aw, no!
Aw...
Huh...
I guess we're gonna have to...
Oh, we're gonna go...
This is gonna take a million years!
Did we bring enough snacks for this journey?
Let me fast forward here.
Bye-bye, Minmus!
And there she blows.
I'm homeward bound.
Oh...
Okay.
We are now officially...
Actually, not yet.
We're not outside of the sphere of influence just yet.
I guess it doesn't want us to speed up when we're at that edge.
Yeah, this is gonna take a million years.
I'm so sorry, Cargill!
This is the craziest first mission of all time for you.
Whee!
Okay, slow down now.
Speed up a bit.
Okay, we're at Apoapsis now.
It's time to burn.
Let's all pray together...
To the Kerbal Gods...
That we make it home on the tank we have.
Also, what's the battery like?
128!
We are...
Chilling with the battery.
No problem.
Here we go.
Double check, we are burning retro.
Good.
We have it on orbit.
Let me actually...
Maybe I should target...
Kerbin for this.
I don't know if it'll make a difference.
Oh, fo...
I guess focus Kerbin is fine.
Oh, this should be fine!
We're chilling!
Whoa!
Yeah, dude, no problem.
Holy shit.
I am a little afraid though of the speed we're gonna be coming in at here.
There we go.
Phew!
That's...
That's gonna take a while.
It's been 48 days and it's almost two months!
Cargill!
Good thing we stuffed enough snacks in there for you.
We actually planned for multiple people but forgot to unpack the snacks.
So you're lucky, actually.
Cargill is coming back.
Oh, speeding up.
You ready to slow down.
Slow down, slow down, slow down, slow down, turbo!
There we go.
Minimus Explorer is on its last legs here.
There we go, man.
We gotta get closer though.
So I currently have it at 24.
I think I'm actually gonna speed up just a bit.
I'm gonna go prograde a bit because we have fuel.
Actually, no, no.
Maybe I should slow down.
Even more.
Oh wait, no!
We're gonna be touching down on the dark side.
Yeah, let's go prograde.
Prograde it is.
Like that.
30.
40.
Actually, I'm just gonna...
Ah, shit.
So if I get to here...
Right before we enter the atmosphere...
We're at 160 now.
And I'm gonna burn retro and we're gonna...
Use our whole tank.
And hopefully we somehow come down over there.
So right about...
Now.
Okay.
Now we turn retro.
This is not very well planned.
I'm gonna use the whole tank.
There we go.
I mean, we're probably gonna...
Come through and then come around and back again.
I mean, it's already been 65 days, you know?
It's gonna be okay.
What's a co- Oi!
Detach!
Uh oh.
Oh shit!
Get out of my way!
I didn't realize we were this far down!
Oh shit!
Cargo!
Hold on to your pants!
Oh my goodness.
Okay, I think we're...
I think we're cool.
We're definitely cool.
Whew!
That was scary.
We still have a problem though, which is...
We don't actually have the ability to...
SAS on to retrograde.
So we're gonna have to manually adjust as we come down.
Slightly, you know?
How's the heat shield doing?
180, okay.
Should be fine.
I'm coming home with a lot of science.
And I mean a lot.
Let's see the orbit.
Decreasing because we're bleeding speed.
Oh my god.
Cargo!
You're almost at the finish line.
You got this.
We may have to take another trip around the planet though.
Is what me thinks.
Actually, I kind of regret burning on the way in.
I'm trying to keep...
Uh, the angle here.
Or the, um...
The ball on the retrograde marker.
Like, exactly at all times.
Yeah, we're starting to, uh...
Go higher up in the atmosphere now.
So we're gonna come around, I think.
Unless we slow down so much that we're actually gonna touch down on the...
Bright side?
Could be!
There's a chance!
It's a small one.
Nah, we're not slowing down enough now.
We're too high up.
Are we?
Maybe.
How's the...
Shield doing?
Okay, 140.
What if you just stack them?
Like...
One heat shield, then another one on top of that.
Double the ablator.
Apoapsis...
It's coming down!
But it's not gonna be enough.
Not this time.
I think we got it in the bag, though.
We're chilling.
Actually, Apoapsis is at 85 now.
Whoop!
Camera change.
This is so awkward, though.
I'm gonna speed up a bit.
Let me angle this a little better.
Actually, look at Apoapsis now.
60 kilometers.
It's very responsive when you're in time warp.
As soon as we cross Apoapsis, we're gonna start to slow down again.
I guess we're already slowing down.
Wait, what?
Why are we pointing this way?
Oh, never mind.
It looked like Prograde, but it isn't.
I was bamboozled.
Hey, we are gonna have a touchdown on the lit side of Kerbin after all.
That actually makes me excited.
Very happy about that.
And we're starting to descend again.
Oh, look at that.
Sunrise.
Cargill!
How are we doing on battery?
112, oh my god.
When do you even need more than one battery pack?
I guess if you're going really far out.
Okay, let's angle this correctly now.
It's definitely a lot easier when you have a pilot that can focus on retrograde.
I would not want to flip over here and become a bullet.
I'm not gonna speed up anymore.
We're gonna keep it on 1x now just to play it safe.
Cheers, guys.
Happy Saturday.
I'm gonna celebrate prematurely here.
Cargill has done it, man.
First mission...
It wasn't a, you know, a landing, but...
I would say for a first flight, very respectable.
Good job, Cargill.
Let's see the ablator.
Half is gone, interesting.
I guess one way you can always make sure that you're gonna come in and not be very fast is you burn to...
Let's say you're in the outer solar system, right?
And you want to come back to Kerbin.
So you basically burn retrograde until periapsis is like, let's say, 80 kilometers.
Then when you reach, uh...
Apoapsis, you burn retro again until periapsis is about the same.
Or even less, you know, and then you keep burning on the...
On the other side constantly until you're slowed down enough, so you don't...
Come in at a crazy high speed, right?
Doesn't that look like Italy over there, that shadow?
Look at that.
It's like the, uh...
Boot.
Just, uh, you know, mirrored.
Looks a bit like Italy.
Time for the chutes!
Now, play it safe.
This is looking very nice.
There we go!
Drogues chutes are up.
Let's take a look out the window.
Oof!
Kinda messed up that you're sitting upside down, right?
And then when we reach, I don't know...
5,000 or so, we're gonna deploy the other chutes.
Or the other chute, I should say.
Oh!
Oh, thank god.
There are some hitches here and there.
But I also have this game modded the fuck out, you know, so...
Probably has something to do with that.
This shit is modded to the brim, man.
So at 2,500, the drogues deploy...
But you can actually adjust this.
You can, uh, right click the chutes when you're building it, and set it to deploy at a different height.
Or even a pressure.
Yeah, this is a splashdown, look at that.
In fact, how close are we to the center?
Where's my guy?
Oh, I'm here.
Wait!
We're right off the coast!
Is it that way?
No way.
Aha!
I guess they can come catch us with a boat.
I mean, I guess they would do that in any case, but you know.
No helicopter required here.
And there she blows.
Let's see here.
Return to Kerbin.
This one is gonna...
uh, activate when we come back.
Oh, I forgot about this one.
Scientific data from space around Kerbin.
I messed up on that.
We definitely could have taken another crew report or something.
Too bad.
Slow down.
Cargill, are you ready?
And...
Splash down!
Of...
The Minmus Explorer.
First iteration.
Come back.
What a beautiful first mission.
And we have 285 science!
What the fuck?!
Also, cargo leveled up, so we can now do pro grade and retro grade holds.
That's amazing.
What am I gonna get?
Also, 775,000 in the bank now.
That really gave us a lot of money.
What's all this?
A hinge!
What?!
There's...
Hydraulic cylinders!
I guess we can stage a car crash now.
For the... for the movies.
Structural tubes.
Airstream protective shells.
That looks like a big decoupler.
Service module.
A service bay with explosive doors.
Do not open by hand.
Okay.
Protective rocket nose cone.
This looks pretty cool!
I like this selection here.
That's in the running.
What about this?
Aerodynamics.
Propeller blades!
What?!
Wait, okay.
I knew you could make aircraft, but...
Propeller aircraft?!
That's crazy.
Cargo storage units.
I don't know what I want.
What about this one?
Oh!
There could be three people in this...
Whoa!
Fly-by-wire avionics hub.
Oh, I thought this was mystery goo, but like a bigger one.
They... they fooled me.
Dude, there's so many things.
Mobility enhancer.
Haha.
Alright then.
I... I feel like I want this.
I want the EVX...
So, we're gonna get this one.
That's 90.
Electrics.
What's that gonna lead to?
Bigger battery?
Two batteries in one.
Light strip.
A Cal-1...
Wait, is that...
A reference to hell?
A first of its kind?
This intelligent, programmable controller can manage a number of parts across a vessel.
It's not an entirely autonomous entity...
Yet.
Okay.
Sure, buddy.
Um...
The thing is though, I need to see what comes after.
I need to plan ahead here.
Oh, I cannot get any of these yet.
Because I have to upgrade.
So I can only get stuff like this.
This doesn't seem exciting to me.
This seems good.
I feel like I want this.
I'm taking this.
And then we have space exploration.
Hmm...
What I want is...
Different landing legs.
Like larger ones.
Scanning tech?
What the fuck?
Is that legs?
Oh, that's more like rover stuff.
Advanced landing.
This could be it, I guess.
Oh.
But I can't get it.
What's that one?
Um...
Okay.
Do I want this at all?
I don't think I do.
This seems pretty cool.
So we have 190 now.
Which means we can get two more.
Let's see what comes after.
So that's that.
And then precision engineering.
Oh my god.
What?
I don't even know what half of this stuff is.
I mean, I guess I want this.
Experiment control station, right?
Like that sounds awesome.
I could also save, you know?
Let's say I wanted some of...
Hold on.
How much does it cost to upgrade?
900.
Wow.
Oh.
And that's what we need to get surface samples.
Hmm.
I feel like we should save...
Our science here.
So let's say I could buy some of these.
What would I get?
What am I missing?
I'm missing...
Bigger landing legs.
Right?
Advanced landing.
I feel like I would get this.
Because we can get it.
Assuming we can upgrade.
What's this?
Light duty rotor.
What's that for though?
Oh, it's probably for...
Propellers?
Or...
That's a big heat shield.
That's a big boy.
I feel like I don't really...
Okay, this one though.
We gotta take this.
Give me that.
We need the EVA experiments kit.
That's probably gonna net us a lot of science.
Okay, let's see here.
Contract time.
What do we have?
Uh, yeah, right.
Okay.
Test mainsail liquid fuel engine.
On a suborbital trajectory over Kerbin.
Man, that's gonna give me a lot of money.
Between 100,000 and 110.
Science data from surface of the moon.
Wait, ferry for tourists.
Complete each tourist's travel itinerary.
And return them safely to Kerbin on schedule to collect their fares.
Oh!
They wanna...
Are you crazy?
They wanna go on an orbit around minmoons.
They wanna land on the moon, bro, in your dreams!
You give me 6,000 for that?
I need 60,000 for that at least!
Are you kidding me?
These guys are making it sound like what I'm doing here is easy.
Hell no.
Bring green sandstone.
What?
Find a green sandstone, have a Kerbal pick it up and return it to Kerbin.
We suspect you can find one of these in the Great Flats.
Greater Flats or Flats biomes.
Oh, it's on Minmoosh.
Okay.
For a second I thought maybe they meant Kerbin.
Cause that's a green planet in a way.
But I guess it's mostly blue.
That's a lot of money.
But...
I don't know.
I couldn't even find a moonstone.
And I feel like I need the surface sample thing to do this, so I'm not gonna take it yet.
Yeah.
Explore Kerbin.
Docking on or around Kerbin is a stepping stone to building greater things.
Plus, it's one of the few times when ramming things together is encouraged.
Dude, I kinda wanna try docking.
Do I have what I take for that?
Or what it takes?
Did I get that via this?
Isn't it that one?
Clam... Oh, it's Clampatron.
Do I really wanna do it then?
I don't wanna use their products.
Oh, you know what?
At some point we have to, you know, forgive and forget.
I'm sure the people responsible for that whole disaster were fired from Clampatron.
I think we have a good relationship with Clampatron now.
Right?
It's not that bad.
Yeah.
I mean...
I wonder how this is gonna work.
I guess we just have a docking port on two vessels and bring them together and it's...
Whoop-de-doo!
Bob's your uncle.
Let's try it.
God, this is ugly.
I mean, beautiful.
Rocket.
So beautiful.
Dude, imagine the science we're gonna get if we go on the moon surface though.
Right?
Like, holy shit, we're gonna get so much science if we do that.
Hmm.
Maybe we should do that first.
There's gotta be more contracts for Minmus.
What else can I do?
I mean, there's this one.
I mean, we can have seven.
Let's just take it.
Let's see if we can find a green sandstone.
Oh fuck, we probably need the surface samples.
I'm an idiot.
I can't believe I did this.
Wait a minute.
We also get money for accepting contracts though.
Hold on.
Advance.
Why wouldn't I just take every contract?
Plant flag on the moon.
I mean, that one's easy.
That's money right there.
Conduct temperature surveys of the...
Oh, but this is in very specific spots, I guess.
It is a lot of money we get.
Hmm.
Oh, this is a tough choice, man.
I guess this one is a no-brainer.
Science data from the surface of the moon.
Boom.
Dude, we're gonna make a rocket?
We will design a rocket that goes to the moon and to Minmus.
We're going all out with this.
And maybe we can even do this one.
We gotta test a mainsail liquid fuel engine.
Nah.
Let's go to the moon.
And then if we have stuff left over, we can go to Minmus after.
Because think about it.
We're already gonna be all the way out there, right?
It's not gonna be as much Delta V that we need.
Okay, so we need the ultimate rocket.
I think the ultimate rocket is Minmus Maximus.
But modified.
God, it's actually beautiful.
Holy shit, I was cooking with this.
Damn.
Damn, that's nice.
Okay, let's see if we can't...
So, I wanna bring a scientist.
So that we can reset experiments.
This is actually such a big deal.
Imagine the riches and the fame and the science we're gonna get out of this.
The papers we're gonna write!
Um...
I will...
disengage that.
And...
Hmm...
See, this is now weird, isn't it?
I could bring a scientist...
instead of a pilot.
But it means we're not gonna have SAS, which is...
kinda... scary.
Like, I don't like that too much.
We do have a battery already, nice.
Okay, so battery's there, let's check.
I guess we don't need the Science Junior for this one.
We also got some more stuff here.
So wait, this one...
This one can have two people.
I question though, like...
Re-entry with this seems kinda...
messed up, doesn't it?
But I guess you wanna put a heat shield here?
Wait, I have an idea.
New craft, I need to test something.
Wait, what?
Oh, right there.
This is the one.
I need to see where the center of mass is here.
Okay, so it's actually near the bottom.
That means it should come in at this...
direction, like going down, you know?
I mean, we can try a rocket like...
Let's try a rocket with this.
We can bring two people, this is like insane.
Lander can.
This actually looks kinda dope.
But maybe we keep it simple for now.
Simple, simple, simple.
Um...
I guess in the end, we want to have...
Wait a minute, we also have this now.
A service bay with explosive doors.
Wait, what is that?
Wait, are you saying that...
This shroud is gonna explode?
What is this one?
Oh, that's a big one, holy shit!
Oh, there's room for all the experiments here.
Hold on now.
Whoa.
I'm getting so overwhelmed now with all these new thingies.
What is this?
Airstream protective shell.
While the Kerbals at Mission Control were still figuring out how to get their rockets back down to Kerbin safely, the research engineers at FLOYD were quickly realizing that protecting parts on ascent was just as important.
Heavy research into two-dimensional input-driven procedural construction was then funded with the hopes of making protective shells for important payloads and interstage areas of the crafts.
The protective shells also have the benefit of making the craft more aerodynamic.
Hopefully saving on precious rocket fuel.
Ah, okay.
1.25 meters.
2.25 meters.
So, it's like making things aerodynamic, I guess.
I don't know if I want to buy it, though.
I mean, I have a lot of money.
I'll buy it.
It's not even that much it costs.
Toggle... wait, hold on.
Place cross-section.
Wait, wait, wait.
Can I go back?
Oh, my God.
That's amazing!
Oh,
that's so cool!
I mean, that's one way to make this more aerodynamic.
Clamshell deploy.
Truss structure?
I don't know what this means.
Interstage nodes.
Whoa, wait.
What?
It's like you can have a payload in there.
Oh, God.
I'm so overwhelmed right now.
There's also all this?
Oh, yeah.
This one.
Let's buy it.
Oh, that's tiny!
What the heck?
Oh, hey, look.
There's a little hatch there.
Oh, that's funny.
Do I have to turn around, though?
Oh, that kind of looks like there...
But that doesn't make any sense.
But I guess you wouldn't put this on now.
You would put this on another vessel, right?
And then...
Like, I guess you would rotate it.
Like that.
Or something.
Oh, God.
This needs planning.
Like, you need to sort of...
Look ahead here.
Oh, my God.
Um...
I am overwhelmed.
Stack separate.
I don't want to spend all my money.
Okay, so we also have all this now.
Hinges.
Mo... Oh.
Target angle.
Oh, and then you can, I guess...
Auto shift state.
What the fuck, dude?
Wait, I forgot what was default here.
I...
Hold on.
Bring it back.
Oh, no.
Did I mess it up?
You know what?
We're gonna...
We're gonna do a little experimenting here now.
We're gonna take a cheap thingy like this...
Come up here.
Like that?
We're gonna put a frickin' hinge on it.
Wait, where did I have it?
Boom.
There's a hinge.
And...
Target angle...
Oh, okay, so this is what you want it to be.
But it's not gonna be when we launch?
Let's see.
Let's just see.
This isn't an experiment.
Motor.
Oh, I see!
Okay, okay, so I...
Oh, that's cool.
So I can adjust it.
I thought I had to set a target angle.
Then I click a button and it goes...
To that angle, you know what I mean?
So, motor disengaged.
Now I can't do it anymore.
Got it.
This is the traverse.
Like how fast it's gonna...
That's actually...
Wait.
Guys.
These are landing legs.
If you think about it.
Oh my god.
Hold on.
Torque limit?
Are you saying...
Oh, that...
There's still a little...
Okay, wait.
Let me put the limit all the way to zero.
What then?
And then it's not gonna work.
But let me put it at...
One.
Let's see if it actually...
Pushes it up.
It doesn't...
Look, it doesn't have enough force now.
Or torque, I guess, in this case.
But now we do.
That's sick.
That's hot.
Oh, that's hot.
Very, very cool.
I'm liking the hinge.
I'm a hinge enjoyer.
Okay.
That's actually pretty damn cool.
What else can I do?
Let's...
Robotics.
Rotate...
Okay, we're gonna...
We're gonna try all this stuff.
So I guess I know what a hydraulic cylinder is, but...
Is it a one-time use?
Like, is it explosive or something?
No, it's hydraulic, I guess, is what it says.
Hahaha.
Um...
Let's try it.
Fuck it.
Wait!
Uh...
Extension
limits...
I...
But I guess this is something I also...
Adjust live?
Damping.
I mean, let's just...
Try it, I...
This is a bad idea.
Please don't start extended.
Oh my god.
Oh, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Uh...
Slowly...
Oh!
Okay.
But hey, you know what the good news is?
Now we're not upside down.
Look.
Hey!
That's...
That's a W right there, I think.
I mean...
Cool.
So I guess you wanna start like that, right?
And then you go like this.
Alright.
I mean...
Testing.
Testing is good.
It feels good, man.
Let's test more.
I mean, that was bound to be bad, you know?
Like...
I was afraid this maybe, uh...
Was gonna blow up or something.
Depending on how fast we...
Fell over, but...
That should be fine.
Look at all this stuff!
RCS ports!
Maybe we should try playing with that, actually.
That's the one where you have to use, like, I, J, and K.
These weird ass fucking keybinds.
But wait.
Let me just have a look.
Wait, I...
What the fuck is this?
What?!
I have big landing legs?!
Since when?!
Oh my god!
Hold up!
We don't need the hinge at all!
Hold up, we're making a sick...
Uh, thingy now.
Watch this.
You kidding me, man?
Parachute.
Two of these.
Boom.
Speed building.
Now we need, uh...
We need something to...
Structural, I guess?
No, we need...
Payload.
This is like the...
The big version of this.
But that's horrible looking.
I don't...
I don't like that.
Maybe it's fine.
Let's put some stuff in there.
Science.
Experiment storage unit?
For sure you know it.
It barely fits.
Actually, we can put it like there.
That's nice.
Maybe don't do that.
What is that stuff at the bottom?
Oh, it's just a visual thing.
Then we can...
Move it like this.
Dude, that looks nice.
Doesn't it?
Maybe even move it down a bit.
Like there.
Okay, that's one thing.
Then we have a mystery goo.
We can put that there.
And then we rotate.
Speed builder.
It needs to look nice.
You know, it's actually kind of important that it looks nice.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god, it's gonna be so sick.
Barometer.
Let's...
I'm gonna put this sort of a little bit everywhere.
So we distribute the weights slightly.
And then we have a thermometer.
Let's put that there.
We're also gonna have...
A...
Let me think.
Cargo?
Oh, this one!
Wait, for some reason I thought this was something that would go in...
This is...
Okay, I thought this was just something the Kerbals were gonna have.
When I unlocked it.
This is a cargo part that can be placed inside inventories.
Okay.
So I do...
How do I...
Wait, how do I do that?
Is it like here?
Inventory...
Oh!
Wait, did that change the look of it?
No.
Oh, that's sick!
What's this one?
ED monitor.
What would happen if you left some mystery goo sitting around in the weird radiation and slash or atmosphere of some faraway planet?
Because I thought that has occurred to nearly every Kerbal, okay.
So we...
That can be placed inside inventories.
And we can deploy it.
Surface deployed mystery goo observations.
Requires an atmosphere.
Does not...
Requires no atmosphere.
Okay, so...
You can place it anywhere, I guess?
Just like on the ground.
Fuck it!
We're putting it in there!
Um...
Alright.
What about batteries?
That's what we need next.
Let's put a battery in here.
I'm even gonna rotate it.
Let's put it like there.
God, this looks so dope, man!
Oh my god!
I hope we get more science stuff so I can fill this up completely, you know?
I wanna be ultimate science man.
Alright.
Now that we did that...
I'm actually gonna save it so far.
So this is gonna be...
Minmus...
Science vessel.
Vessel?
MSV.
Uh...
We shall go there...
And collect the sour.
Cover it up!
Can I even change the look of it?
Ah, that's inside, I guess.
Okay.
Okay!
Uh, let's change the color of this to...
Yeah, I like that.
I like that.
That's nice.
Dude, this is gonna be so sick!
What the fuck?
Now wait, we wanna come back with this, I guess.
So, let me see the weight right now.
Ooh!
Yeah, I don't like that!
Uh-oh.
This means we're probably gonna flip on re-entry.
Wait, shit.
Also, I forgot something.
Uh...
No, I didn't.
Wait, how the hell?
Guys, I think it's time we start communicating.
Antenna time!
Wait, let me see something.
Antenna type...
Relay...
Electric...
F-fifty-one per second?!
Huh?
Are you saying it's gonna drain my battery in three seconds?
Oh...
Uh-oh.
This one is twenty per second!
We need to...
We need to recharge...
Fucking solar panels, man.
Solar...
Panels...
I don't even know if I have that.
Where would that be?
I saw them somewhere.
I may not have unlocked them.
Oh, no!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What?
How do I come home?
Maybe I can...
Um...
Oh, shit.
We have a problem.
Ah, but wait, wait, wait.
Let me try something.
So, we also have thermal.
It does shift the...
Center of mass down slightly, but...
I mean, honestly, maybe this is fine.
You know?
In fact, you know what we should do?
It's not gonna...
Make a dent, I think, but...
I'm gonna put all of these...
On the lowest...
Part here.
Just shift the mass down slightly.
That's probably not gonna change shit, is it?
Eh.
But, you know.
Also, what about this antenna?
That's gonna burn up, isn't it?
Holy...
Uh...
I'm actually facing kind of a problem here.
A shift in...
I think the game is telling me to...
Start using...
The communication channels here, you know?
And start...
Sending science down from up there, and not actually bringing it back.
I think that's what the game is telling me.
But fuck, I...
I...
I can't do that.
Wait.
I'm a dumbass.
No.
I'm actually not a dumbass.
I'm kinda...
The opposite right now.
Ah, this...
Man, this game is tough!
What the fuck?
This is...
Suddenly...
Difficult.
Um...
Also, what am I even trying to do here?
I'm...
I guess I'm trying to go and land on Minmus.
And bring a lot of science back, right?
That's the whole point.
It's a Minmus lander mission.
Then we have that, and...
We transmit back...
Oh god, I mean...
Wait, let me actually try something.
Save this vessel.
Let's see if we can...
Buy a solar panel.
I guess that would be down here near electrics.
Is that it?
Solar panel there.
Thermal control system.
Ah, man.
I wanted to save my science, but...
Fuck it!
I'm buying it.
I have so many new parts now.
So many new...
What is that one?
Probodobodyne Octo.
The Octo is the next step in unmanned control technology.
This small unit can not only receive and relay control, it also provides automatic stabilization assistance.
Just as a live pilot would.
Also, it's eight sided stylistic design features lots of flat surfaces for attaching equipment.
Wait a minute.
Are you saying...
That I can bring a scientist, have this in here...
And get the benefits of a pilot without having a pilot?
Brother.
Wait a minute.
I need to investigate something.
Show me...
The...
Minmus...
Moonlander.
If I open this up here...
I mean, obviously there's no space now.
Yeah.
But I think that's what that means.
That's pretty cool, I guess.
I'm still gonna roll with this one.
We may have to do a little bit of a test here.
Okay?
This is a test flight.
Yep.
Time for testing.
We're gonna put a little heat shield...
On...
This is gonna...
Fuck up my measurements though a little bit, isn't it?
Because this is gonna add weight.
But I guess it's fine.
You know what?
Coming through dense atmosphere is probably gonna be a good enough test.
So we don't need this.
Let's keep it like that.
We're gonna do a decouple here.
Oh, that's... holy shit, that's a big one.
That's what we need.
And then let's just have a simple ass...
Engine.
Maybe...
Holy shit, that's big.
Yeah, why not?
No...
Yeah, that's fine.
Engines...
I guess it's this one.
It's gonna cost 12,000, but it's fine.
This is a test.
So we have this one.
Also, we haven't even tested whether or not this big ass pod is gonna be fine with the amount of shoots that we have.
Let me see the pod.
14 meters per second impact, okay.
So we do that.
And then we come down.
This one.
That one.
These ones first.
What the fuck is that?
Wait, what?
Oh!
When I...
When I put this on, this appears!
What?!
What does that mean?
Wait, hold on.
We gotta test that first.
We're doing two tests here!
I guess put that...
Wait, what happened?
Now it's gone.
What the...
Now it's back.
Okay.
Put this here.
Put that there.
We...
Honestly, we don't need these for this test.
What does this mean?
What does that mean?
Oh!
Oh shit!
Uh oh.
Does it matter, maybe?
We're gonna come down with the...
doors open?
I mean...
It's gonna be covered by the...
surface area down there.
I think it's fine.
For some reason, I thought I could just open and close this, just like the other service bay.
Wait, why can't I come back?
What?
Let me come back...
Space center?
Recover.
Weird that I couldn't do that from the pad.
Okay.
Whatever.
We continue with the test.
Let me just open the...
thing again here.
There we go.
No, not that one.
The other one.
This one.
Okay, fuck it.
This one's probably gonna...
blow up.
But probably not on this test.
Right click that...
and retract it.
Alright, let's continue the test.
Now we needed this guy.
And then an engine.
Just like that.
So this one.
That one.
Yeah, I guess that's fine.
So we do this.
Now we do that.
We can even do that before.
Yeah.
That's good.
Bup, bup.
Bup, bup, bup.
I'm only gonna bring one guy.
I don't wanna accidentally kill someone here.
Bill, you're not coming.
Carson, you're too valuable.
It's gotta be...
It's gotta be Bill.
Bill, you're flying this thing.
Then again.
I would love to have some kind of SAS here for the test.
Actually, this would be an even better test.
Bill, you're up.
Here we go.
Oh, we can't do SAS.
Right.
Oh, oh, oh my god.
It's...
Very sensitive.
Oy, oy, oy, oy, oy, oy.
Bill!
Oh shit!
Oh no!
Uh oh.
Stop the engine.
We may have to detach.
Fuck it.
Turn around.
Oh no.
Hey, the fact that it doesn't wanna turn around on its own is actually good.
Oh, but I guess that's because we're heavy down...
Here.
Yeah, this is not a good test actually.
We need to do this angle.
Follow retro.
And see what happens.
Is it gonna stabilize on its own?
Let's see.
Looks like it.
I'm not inputting anything right now.
Oh shit.
Look, even with this amount of wobble, it's still stabilizing.
That's very good news.
Okay.
There goes the other part.
Okay, I think that's a successful test.
I think we have proved that this thing is stable in flight.
Oh, what's that?
Oh, the other part.
Where's that gonna crash?
Somewhere over there.
Hopefully nobody got hit by that.
It was very close to...
Uh, I think that is the...
Astronaut facility where they hang out.
Bill, good test.
Good job.
I'm proud of you.
Has Bill even flown yet?
I feel like he's the first...
This is the first time he's ever flown.
You know?
Okay.
Very nice.
The theory is sound.
Now we make the rocket.
Actually, I kinda like this part here.
So we do that.
No, wait.
We're gonna take this.
I'm gonna do that.
So right now we're making the lander.
Now we want...
This one.
Because it has good ISP.
And since we have amazing legs...
Wait, they kinda look small now.
Oh my god.
Fuck me, they're small.
They look much bigger on the small rocket.
Oh no.
But I guess it's almost...
Long enough.
If we can drag it down just slightly.
Let's add more.
Four of them.
Like that.
I mean...
I think that's okay.
I kinda like.
I do.
Now we adjust it.
No.
Make it like that.
Attach.
Hey, I like that.
That's not too bad.
It looks a little janky, but you know.
Kerbals live janky lives.
So it's okay.
That actually looks kinda dope.
Me like.
Now we do a couple.
Coupling.
Oh, this is a thick rocket though.
And then we need...
That one.
I guess I can do a little extra.
Oh wait, these are the really big ones now.
These two together.
Let's make them orange.
Yeah.
And then for the engine...
Wait, why is it doing that?
Oh wait, that's the small one.
Wow, that's a strong...
Guys.
It's already 24,000.
This is an expensive boy.
Holy shit.
But we're not done.
Wait, does this gimbal?
Yeah, it has a little bit of vector...
Vectoring range.
Let's add another...
Decoupler.
And then we add...
That one?
I need a...
Do I not have a bigger one?
Oh my god, I need a bigger one!
Oh no.
Maybe it's fine.
Hey wait, I can put them on the side.
Let's do the side ones.
Also, we need to be within parts.
23 parts.
Radial decoupler.
Let's do two.
Oh yeah.
And then...
The question is which ones?
These ones?
Holy shit.
That's...
Oh wait, I think I need to adjust these legs a little bit.
Like that.
And then we have to move them again.
Oh, this is...
Awkward now.
Wait, hold on.
Show me.
Yeah, this is looking...
Oh!
Hella awkward.
Man, they're barely holding on though.
I don't know if I like that.
We need to put them a little higher.
Let's see what they look like.
Ah, it's still good.
I... I... okay.
Yep, that's good.
Very nice.
Shroud on.
Man, this is a 37,000...
Man, this is a very expensive rocket.
Hmm.
Maybe we don't need these big ones.
Let's just calm down a bit.
We can put these guys on.
Wait.
It didn't add that much.
What about these guys?
I don't like this rocket very much.
Am I...
Okay, check it out.
We're not gonna do any solid boosters at all on this.
We're just gonna add more tanks.
Let's just try that.
Hell yeah.
So we go like this.
Hot damn!
It's not the prettiest rocket, but you know.
It's cool.
And then we have people in here.
We're gonna bring...
I think it's time for Carson.
Definitely Carson.
And then we're gonna bring Bob.
Carson and Bob.
And let's just confirm here.
So on the way home...
So we do this one first.
The bottom one.
Decouple that one.
We do that together.
Actually, we don't need to.
We're gonna be quite high.
Oh, we also have this thing.
Yeah, that's fine.
So...
Oh, but wait a sec!
If I deploy this, what happens to the antenna?
Oh shit!
Also, we need a way to recharge here.
Electrical.
I need this.
Sun tracking.
Oh my god, it's tiny!
Wait, let me see.
Electric charge...
0.3 per second!
Ah, but wait a minute!
The whole idea now is that we don't...
We don't use this anyway, right?
Because...
We're gonna come home with this.
That was the whole plan.
We tested that.
It should work.
We're fine.
One other thing I could do...
Is...
If things go really bad...
I could have another decoupler here...
Just to detach this guy.
But that's gonna add mass up here, which is not great.
But it is an emergency thing, right?
What does this look like on other versions?
Oh, that...
Wait, what?
Wait a sec!
That was a difference in height!
I wonder!
Okay, there's...
There's nothing that's like...
Tinier.
Okay, that's fine.
So we used the first one.
Oh my god, man.
That's interesting.
I mean, okay.
I think I like that.
It looks super simple!
Wait, 3600...
Delta V.
Um...
Doesn't feel like a lot, does it?
We had a rocket that did 5000.
Wait, I...
We need to make this better.
We need solid rocket boosters, man.
We do, we need it.
You know what we could do?
We could just add another stage.
Let's say this is the bottom stage.
We have a stage in between.
So think of it like the first stage getting us out of the atmosphere.
The other one is going to get us into orbit.
The last one is going to take us around the solar system, you know?
So which engine would I use there, I guess is the question.
Well, I guess I'm...
Hmm.
Yo, check it out.
We're going to add more fuel to this.
Wait, hold on.
What?
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Oh no.
What's wrong?
It won't connect now.
Oh wait, now it does.
Oh, this is a mess?
This is a mess.
I'm going to add more fuel up here.
That's a thick boy.
Holy shit.
Four of them.
We're going to have to move this slightly.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes.
That looks good.
Attach it again.
Let's double check.
Beautiful.
Nice.
I mean, it's going to be different when we're in space, right?
Okay.
Also, we can look at this thing here.
I mean, look, in vacuum, obviously, we have a lot more.
So at sea level, this one's going to give us 2,000...
Oh, that's actually a lot.
And then when we're in vac...
Oh my...
Hold on.
That's crazy.
Okay, this rocket is actually banging.
It doesn't look like it, but it's going to bang.
Okay.
We're off.
It's time.
Carson, Bob...
Save the vehicle.
Let's launch.
Wish me luck.
Okay.
And...
Okay, so it turns out...
We just don't have enough force to even get off the ground.
Nice.
Let's...
Let's run that back.
I didn't even look at the thrust to weight ratio.
What the fuck?
Oh, it's 0.83.
Holy...
Okay.
I guess we do need some boost arenos here.
I can't believe it.
Wait, we also have these.
Just bigger ones, I guess.
Bigger and better.
Yeah, let's have those.
We're gonna add two of these.
That actually looks nice.
We're gonna add...
Kickback!
Should we go all out on this?
Dude, that...
This rocket actually looks amazing.
Love the way this looks!
And look, look here.
1.02!
Ooh!
I feel like...
We need even stronger.
1.36.
Okay, see, that I can deal with, you know?
Also, I'm not happy about this placement.
We're gonna put this a little higher.
Like there.
And...
And these...
Man, this is gonna be an expensive rocket.
Move these down slightly.
Just so when we detach here, they're gonna fly that way and not like...
It's not gonna be like this angle.
It's gonna be like that angle, you know what I mean?
A little further down, maybe.
Okay.
Now we're gonna add...
Do we have some aerodynamicism?
Let me see this one.
That's a bit too big.
What about that one?
Ooh, that's perfect!
Oi yoi yoi!
Oh my god, this rocket is amazing looking.
Wait, we're exactly at 30, so that means it's okay.
We're cool, right?
Did we actually do it in exactly 30?
So let's see, so we do these two.
Wait a sec!
Oh, now we have plenty!
Oh, I didn't even include this in the initial launch.
Then we detach that.
This gets disattached.
Or disengaged, whatever.
Engine.
Wait, we're missing something here.
We need to...
We don't have a freaking thingy here.
Oh my god!
Dude!
I'm so happy we didn't have enough thrust to weight ratio to take off!
That's crazy!
What the...
I feel like I just... I just got saved there.
God, this rocket is sexy looking, man!
Tell me this isn't the most amazing rocket ever.
It's one... oh no!
Hold on!
Can we upgrade?
I'm gonna do it!
Basic action groups available.
I don't know what that means.
Fuck it!
We are no longer bound by 30 limit!
Hell yeah!
Okay, let's just run this back once more.
Yeah, see it's already wrong.
This goes together with that.
And then these get detached...
When flying, and then...
This one...
And this one together...
This one first, and then we do this one.
Right?
And then these... yeah.
Okay.
Sweet.
I think we got it.
Save now.
Let's see the crew.
Wait, what?
Oh, I guess this is what I unlocked.
Uh-oh, what did I do?
Undo, undo!
Control-C.
Fuck!
Uh-oh.
What have I done?
I don't know what I just did.
Hopefully I didn't do something that's gonna mess me up somehow.
Carson and Bob.
Fuck it, we're just gonna go.
Wish me luck.
The launch pad can't support vessels heavier than 140 tons.
What?!
No!
No, let me see.
Duh-ho!
You gotta be fucking kidding me!
Okay, you know what.
I have an idea.
We don't need these big-ass boosters because I forgot to bring this in the first stage down here, right?
So what we're gonna do instead, we're gonna use the tiny... just to save more weight here.
We're gonna have two of these.
Boom, right?
Now we use smaller boosters.
The kickback.
Is that gonna be enough?
Let's see.
I hate when it does that.
Like, can you please put it on the thing?
Boom.
There we go.
Oh, it is... it is kinda...
Okay, you know what?
I actually don't trust these tiny ones.
That looks a little crazy to me.
Bring these back.
And then...
Kickback.
Let's see what the weight is now.
Okay!
Way less!
Fantastic!
And then we need some aerodynamicism.
Guess it would be that one in this case.
Actually... okay, this also looks kinda dope.
This is also very nice looking.
So these two... is it enough now?
1.5?
That's perfect!
And then these two get detached.
Boom!
This one... boom, boom, boom.
Yeah!
Okay, here we go.
You ready?
Let's just double check the crew.
Carson and Bob.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
And go.
Oh my god.
Oh, this took a while, man.
Making this rocket.
But it's fun.
You ready?
Oh, look at all this.
We can do much more things now.
Okay.
3... 2... 1...
Lift off!
I'm coming.
We're gonna start burning.
Or like turning.
We are burning.
We're gonna start turning at...
2,000.
Now.
Although the vessel does wanna rotate for some reason.
I don't like that.
It doesn't seem to want to...
rotate very much.
Okay, I just gotta deal with the rotation.
Fuck it.
We're keeping the nav ball on the line.
I don't... I... Why is it rotating though?
Maybe we need some fins or something.
Okay.
Can you please stay like this now?
Detach!
Apoapsis.
32.
Just keep it like that, I guess.
I feel like this was not a good launch.
Like, we're only at 700-ish.
And those were some very expensive boosters.
Let's see here.
Okay, looking good.
Actually, this is fine.
This is actually a great launch.
In fact, I'm gonna put it on prograde.
And I'm gonna rotate the ball.
Like that.
Whoops.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
That's too much.
This rocket is not doing well on rotation.
Okay.
64.
Why is this rocket so unstable feeling?
70?
In fact, I'm gonna use the entire fuel on this right now.
Uh, go to stability assist.
Now we go horizontal.
Actually, a little more than that.
This looks weird, but trust me.
Actually, don't trust me.
How do I...
Just, please use the fuel!
Oh my god.
Hold on.
Yeah, let's just do it when we get there.
I think we have enough fuel to actually make it into orbit with this stage, which is crazy.
Oh, that's a bit too fast.
Okay, let's go.
Prograde, go.
This is looking good.
Dude, if we can get to orbit with this stage, it would be so cool.
Come on, baby, come on!
Oh, it's gonna be close.
I don't think we can.
Oh, it's so close!
Bye-bye.
Almost.
There we go.
Dude, look at that orbit, though!
Holy shit!
Nice!
Very nice.
Okay, so now, let's see here.
Dude!
We have two people with us!
Look at this!
This is the first time!
We have a multi-curbable mission!
And you know what?
This rocket doesn't look too bad.
It looks cool!
We got a scientist!
Oh, but I guess I gotta...
Wait, enable cutaway.
I wonder if this is gonna...
Right now.
I guess I could also just click space?
Okay, that's cool!
Oh, that's nice!
That feels so good!
Holy shit!
Oh, that's the battery.
Is there any signs we can even take here that's gonna help us?
This thing!
Hold up, we gotta do some experiments here.
Did it say anything about needing a scientist for this?
I feel like we need a scientist for that.
Bob!
You're up!
Uh, can I somehow...
Inventory...
Wait, you don't need a parachute, do you?
Can I just...
Okay!
So what now?
Let go...
Perform EVA science!
What's that gonna look like?
Let's see here.
I wanna be kinda...
Steady there, there we go.
That's cool!
Watching the astronaut look through the EVA science kit has given us conclusive evidence that the new situation has not improved their creativity.
I knew this.
Oh, this is so good.
But, can I...
Can I retrieve this little...
Thing?
This is actually such a weird phenomenon, by the way.
You can see videos of this on the internet on the space station.
Where they actually perform this.
It's weird how it turns like that, but it does.
Zero-G is weird, man.
What if I bump it?
Oh, there's no collision?
Oh, there is!
Okay, okay.
Wait, let me go...
Oh, wait a minute.
Boop!
Get the visor up.
Oh, I stopped it!
Let me bump into it.
There we go.
Yo, this is so fucking cool!
Oh, my God!
Bob, you deserve this spacewalk.
You really do.
You're the man.
We gotta get inside again.
I guess this is the entrance here.
There we go.
Okay, let's just...
So we have some signs now from the orbit around Kerbin.
That should count.
Yep, so this one is done.
Wait, was I going to the moon or Minmus?
Wait, I was going to the moon!
Because we gotta plant a flag there.
And we gotta transmit stuff from the moon.
But I guess I can go either way.
Let's go to Minmus, and then if we have enough left over, we can go to the moon after.
We'll see how it goes.
Actually, is that going to be awkward?
If we are further out, and then we want to go further in again, that's going to be awkward, isn't it?
I think it's better to start on the moon and then go from there to...
Oh, that's going to be really weird.
We're going to have to wait until they're sort of in alignment?
Hmm.
Okay.
I guess what we can do is perform this, because we can reset it now.
That doesn't really give us much.
But I wonder, did I now consume the EVA experiments kit?
Or can I do it again?
I have a feeling I consumed it, because the little rotating thing is now in space, right?
Now I kind of regret doing it here, and not on Minmus or something.
Damn it.
Okay, whatever.
I don't want to accidentally hit space, that could be really catastrophic.
Let's go to the moon.
Target.
Let me try this again.
I just don't feel like it's that good.
Like, it feels really janky, this system here.
Oh, okay, actually, this was kind of smooth.
Never mind.
This actually worked much better than last time.
Are you kidding me?
I can slow down even more here.
What if I rotate?
Okay, never mind.
I take it back.
This is actually pretty dope.
I like this system.
Okay, now...
So, 844...
Delta V is what we need for this.
Also, last time...
I think I know what's going on here.
So, last time I burned way too early.
I think I have to burn like half of it before we actually hit the node.
Because I thought, for some reason I thought it calculated that for me, such that I just had to burn at that time, you know?
But I don't think that's the case.
We were definitely off.
Um...
Where am I in the orbit?
Okay, it's gonna take a while.
I can also...
Yeah.
So why would you use alarm clocks then, if you can just do this?
Whoa, that's so fast!
Slow down!
Uh...
How are we on battery?
Oh, wait!
We have way more battery now!
I think it's because we have a bigger pod.
That's nice!
So we probably didn't even need to bring that battery pack, really.
Um...
Okay.
So wait, it says, burn time 1 minute and 2 seconds.
So I guess I wanna burn at...
31...
seconds.
Before we hit the node.
Let's also start pointing towards the thing we need to point to.
That way.
Whoa!
Oh, this thing is massive!
You can tell there's a lot of fuel in this bad boy.
It's waiting to come out the butt.
There we go.
Okay, so in...
Uh...
When it's at 31...
Here we go!
Go!
God, this...
lander looks weird.
It's not a very strong engine, is it?
But that's okay.
We're not trying to escape a planet right now.
Well, we are, in a way, but...
You know what I mean?
Not from the ground.
Oh, it looks different!
Hey, my...
Oh my god, look!
What's up, buddy?
I guess...
Who's that?
Who did I just click on?
Oh, that was Bob we were looking at.
So I was controlling cart...
Oh, we gotta be ready to stop here.
Six...
Five...
Four...
Wait, why is it slow?
Stop.
Wait, I am confused by this.
My blue one is my actual one, right?
Yeah, okay.
Okay, so we are on a course...
And we still have lots of fuel, that's fantastic.
We're also gonna perform science there.
Um...
Yo, you know what would be cool?
If we could go to the moon and perform that experiment, you know, the famous experiment with a hammer and a feather.
And see if they fall down at the same time, you know, because there's no air resistance.
That could be cool.
Maybe that's like...
Honestly, maybe that's what the EVA experiment is gonna do when you're on the ground, you know, on another planet or something.
Because obviously you don't want to just throw the little rotating thingy down.
Maybe it's gonna, like, adapt, you know?
Okay, speed up.
I'm coming, moon.
I'm coming.
Look at the signal strength.
It's going down.
In fact, we're actually getting a little gravitational assist here if we keep this course.
We're being pulled in.
And at the time we're over here, the moon is there, so it's still pulling on us slightly.
But I guess the angle is not great.
You want to come out that way, I guess?
I'm not an expert on this, but...
I guess the basics...
are there.
Now...
Where do we land?
Oh, by the way!
Um, apparently we can only find the moonstone in certain places on the moon.
I forgot...
what it's...
I wish I could somehow...
read the...
Oh wait, I guess I can.
I can just go back, can I?
Hold on.
Slow down.
Space center.
I have to remember I can just do this.
And then mission control.
Moonstone.
So...
Polar lowlands.
Farside crater.
Or east crater biomes.
Farside crater sounds to me like...
well, a crater on the far side.
Meaning the side not pointing towards earth.
Holy shit!
That was loud.
The weather's not good back on earth.
I mean, Kerbin.
Let's see here.
This is the far side.
There's not really...
Wait, what's this?
Oh, these are the missions where I have to do something in a specific spot.
Oh my god.
That sounds so difficult, man.
Uh, fly.
Let's see here.
Let's get to Periapsis first.
First things first.
Let's try and land on the Farside crater.
Okay, Periapsis has been reached.
Oh, look at that beauty.
Point retrograde.
We have plenty of batterinos.
What is that planet?
Minmos.
Oh, that's so funny!
We're going there after.
If we can.
God damn, dude.
Burn more and more and more and more and more.
The problem is...
The Farside is dark.
You know?
So I don't know.
I see some big craters here.
And also, I don't really want to land in the dark, man.
Maybe I just kinda...
Maybe we try to go for this one.
You know?
That seems like a big ol' crater.
Let's go to the opposite side here.
Like...
Here.
And we have to turn...
Retrograde again.
God, that moon looks glorious with the Terminator right there.
Let's see.
We're gonna be right on the edge of the crater.
Ooh, that's close.
And I guess when we get there, we can start burning.
Let's do that.
Here we go.
Also, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Double check.
Do we have any assignments about...
Signs around the moon?
Surface of the moon.
Plant flag on the moon.
And a moonstone.
Okay.
This one we already did.
Great.
Radio blackout.
Oh, it's so dark.
Whoa!
Oh wait, is this it?
What's that?
Valentina landing!
There's no way!
You... you get to see that?
Yo, that's so cool!
Wait, so wait, I already landed here then.
I don't wanna land here then.
Oh no wait, that is here!
This is a different one.
I thought we were already over that.
Aha!
Let's keep moving.
So we are gonna be in a different one.
Maybe we can find that moonstone then.
Right here.
Seems like a good spot to do it.
Okay, now we point retrograde.
Man, what a feeling, huh?
Battery?
Perfect.
Let's see.
Ideally, we wanna land...
on a very flat surface.
Let's just stop there.
Oh, let's get the legs out.
Beautiful.
This is routine at this point.
It doesn't look flat, does it?
Like, this is very hilly.
I am not liking this, actually.
Let's burn.
This could maybe be flat?
Oh god, I don't know.
Looking good.
God, this is gonna be hilly as hell, isn't it?
This is not flat.
Also, I don't think we're gonna have fuel for Minmus.
Look at our fuel, man.
It's not great.
Then again, the less fuel we have, the less we weigh.
You know?
So maybe that fuel's gonna last longer.
I mean, it's not a maybe, it is a fact.
Am I really a thousand meters?
That's no way.
There's no way.
Oh no.
Okay, we're not gonna hit the rocks.
Good.
Good, good, good, good, good, good.
Oh no!
What do I do?
Maybe we land down here?
It was gonna tip over.
This looks kinda flat.
Don't land on the rocks.
Oh, you bastard.
Don't do this to me.
Okay, that looks kinda okay, maybe?
Stay, please, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay.
God, why do I...
Why is it always like this?
I feel like this is not stable.
I'm not liking the fact that one of these legs is on one of these rocks.
Look at the way it's wobbling, man!
It's probably fine.
Wait a minute, what the fuck?
How is this...
Not open?
Wait, what?
Didn't I...
That's a bug?
Look at this, I opened this.
When we were in space.
Wait, I can't even get to it now.
Oh no.
Uh, Bob.
What do we do, Bob?
I guess we go plant the flag.
I guess Bob can do it.
Oh, shit.
Uh...
Let go.
RCS.
Jetpack.
Nice.
Whoa.
This rocket is so big now, when you see it from down here.
Look.
It's like massive, dude.
Damn.
That's crazy.
Imagine walking around here.
Wow.
Oh.
We're skipping across the surface.
Where do I put the flag though?
I'm gonna put it over here.
This is a good spot.
EVA science?
He...
He's playing golf?!
Oh my god.
60...
That's crazy!
Watching the astronaut look through the EVA science kit has given us conclusive evidence that the new situation has not improved their creativity.
I would say that's pretty creative.
Good job, Bob.
I didn't take you for a golfing man.
But okay.
Uh...
EVA report.
EVA report from the moon's north west crater.
Okay, so I guess we're not in the far side crater.
Fuck.
You should've brought your golf club.
Hello?
We did that.
Plant flag.
Right here.
Bob's...
Hole in one.
On this...
No.
This...
Is where Bob...
Uh...
Hit a...
Hole in one...
On the first try.
That's beautiful.
Are you okay there, Bob?
Bob?
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
What else can I do?
Um...
Wait, can I do this again?
I guess I don't want to do it again right here.
Jetpack.
Oh, wait!
Now it's open!
Okay, it's bugging.
This is buggy as hell.
Haha.
Sweet.
This rocket has a mind of its own.
Ooh!
Grab it, man!
Nice.
Oh, is it?
Ooh!
God, it feels so janky!
It's almost tipping over!
We gotta collect the signs and get the hell out of here.
Mystery goo.
Observe.
It's less dense here?
Great.
What about this?
They say insanity?
Yeah, yeah.
What's that?
Oh, it's a battery.
Temperature.
The inclined angle of the solar radiation at this latitude has a marked effect on the temperature.
Which you make note of in your report.
Good.
We wanna be thorough here.
What about a crew report?
You feel awestruck at the beaten up nature of the moon.
Hell yeah.
So now, what we wanna do is this.
Transfer.
To there.
This one.
And then I guess we do the goo.
Transfer data.
To there.
And the good news is, we can reset this canister because we have a scientist with us!
Okay.
And that's it, I think.
Let me see this.
Plant flag on the moon.
Done.
Transmit or recover scientific data from the surface.
We have done that.
Moonstone.
I mean...
I guess it's not here then.
We gotta go...
We gotta find the biome that actually says Farsight Crater.
You know?
That's what we need to do.
And you know what's crazy?
I think Valentina Landing was actually the Farsight Crater.
Because it was a huge crater and it was on the far side when we passed over.
So I think the first time we put that flag down there, that was actually the right spot for it.
Which is funny.
But we'll see.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe there's another crater.
Alright.
We're gonna move on now.
Let me see.
This is north.
So we wanna go that way.
The question is of course, which way is that?
I have no...
Oh, I guess if we're pointing here...
That means I gotta...
Wait.
Let me align it.
Then I gotta go...
This way.
I mean, not that it matters.
We're gonna look at the ball, right?
Okay, you ready?
Three...
Two...
One...
Lift off!
Yeah, I definitely miscalculated the path.
Good thing I have the nap ball and not my intuition.
My intuition sucks.
Wow.
Okay, stop burning now.
We're at 18,000 meters apoapsis.
As soon as we get up there, we're gonna start burning prograde and...
Get into orbit.
We...
I guess we could technically go on an EVA now, but that seems crazy, doesn't it?
Is that a bad idea?
No, let's go into orbit and then we EVA.
Yeah.
We're almost there.
I think we can...
Probably do it now.
Okay.
Prograde.
Retract these.
There we go.
Speed.
The first landfall!
Oh my god!
That's right over there?!
Dude, it's so...
I love that you can see that from here.
That's so cool.
Okay, we...
We did a little more extra than we had to here, but that's okay.
I don't think we have enough fuel to go to Minmus.
This seems a little crazy to do.
But...
Is it really crazy?
So Minmus is right there.
I suspect from here...
It's probably gonna be like...
There?
I...
Well, I guess I can sort of just preview.
I can do this stuff.
And I can see how much Delta V costs.
Oh my god, I can actually...
Just do that.
Wait, what?
Ah, but wait, we're not even at the right inclin...
Ah, this is bad.
We would have to burn for inclination first.
Let's just...
Let's take the W and go home.
You know?
Also, I guess I can technically preview what would be best here.
Let's say I do this.
Oh my god, look.
Okay, remember when I was talking about...
It's best to burn right here?
Apparently that was kind of true, but not entirely.
So it seems like the best place to burn...
Is where...
The actual escape trajectory is in the direction...
Opposite of...
Prograde around the...
Kerbin, right?
So it's more like here.
But if I burn over here...
Yeah, it's actually not that great.
But let's not also forget that...
When we burn here, we're gonna be at a different spot around the Kerbin, right?
And that's why.
Wait a minute, this only takes 200 meters per second to do this.
Wait...
Guys...
Hmm...
Hold on a minute.
I mean, we're in orbit, we can chill for a bit.
There's no rush here.
Wait a minute...
Set this guy as a target.
This may be a horrible idea.
Um...
Okay, so that's the target.
This is weird.
See, now I wish I could see some kind of difference in inclination between us.
See, that's not quite right, is it?
Let me put it on target.
I guess we would do approach info.
Hmm...
I'm still not like 100%...
I don't know, like this system is weird.
I'm still not like...
I don't understand it intuitively.
I feel like I would have to zoom out like this and just...
You see that?
That's like the angle.
And I have to sort of...
It's very janky, right?
So...
It would go like that.
Then you would try to match it like this now, but...
There's gotta be like...
A better way.
How do I make this go away?
This one.
Maneuver.
How does that...
Oh, it's because it's the other side.
Oh shit.
So here, we wanna go up.
Ah man, it's...
Let me just try and add a bunch.
Like that.
That's like 500.
Oh, look at that!
Uh...
I can also do this.
That's maybe way too much.
Wait, that's...
No, wait.
This one.
Oh, that...
Wait, what the fuck?
Wanna aim a little ahead?
There we go, there we go, there we go, there we go, there we go.
Minimals encounter.
In one day.
Periapsis of 1,300,000 meters.
And that's gonna cost us...
Ooh, that's 700...
That's no...
That's no way.
I mean, there's probably like a more efficient maneuver I can do here to get to Minimus, but...
I can't be fucking...
Figuring that out now.
That's crazy.
How do I just...
Get rid of that?
We're going home!
Let's not, you know, squeeze the lime too much here.
I feel like the lime has been squozed a lot already, you know?
Okay, I like that.
That's pretty good.
We're gonna do that burn.
In 44 minutes.
And it's only for seven seconds, that's funny.
How are we doing on battery?
Dude, wait, do we like have a...
Alternator!
It is that.
It keeps recharging.
Fast forward.
Please slow down beforehand?
Okay.
Note in one minute.
Man, they make it so easy now with this...
System here.
You know what?
I think it's a good idea we go home, because...
We haven't even...
Tried to...
Re-enter with this setup here.
This is a big...
Problem.
Like, this could go wrong.
We've only tested this in the very low atmosphere, very dense air, you know?
And it seemed to be stable there.
But who knows?
It may not be stable on a re-entry path.
I don't fucking know.
Because remember, on...
On the test that we did, we were facing almost directly down.
Whereas here we're gonna come in at almost horizontal through the atmosphere, you know?
So I don't know if that's gonna mess things up.
So we're gonna burn in...
I guess when it says three seconds or so?
I could just look at the freaking map, no?
Wait!
Stop, stop, stop!
We have it on target!
Wait, what?
Yeah, see?
We fucked up.
No, wait, no, no, stop, stop, stop!
It is procreate.
What am I doing?
Apparently it was just...
Happened to be the same direction.
A little more...
Get rid of this shit.
Wait, something's wrong here.
Let's just get out of...
Orbit here.
I feel like I'm being more confused with this manuring stuff...
Than without it.
But I guess I just gotta get used to it.
Okay.
Now we point retrograde, and we should have plenty of battery.
I'm so nervous about battery ever since that one time.
Holy shit.
And here's what I'm gonna do.
We're gonna burn such that we have about 80 kilometers on periapsis.
Like that.
Okay, that's fine, I guess.
And then when we get there, we're gonna burn again...
To reduce apoapsis so that we can slow down a hell of a lot before we enter the atmosphere.
Just to make it safer.
Here we go.
Periapsis.
Time to burn retro again.
Because look at us, we're coming in really fast, right?
There we go.
Slowing down.
Wait a second.
This is... hold on, I almost fucked up here.
If I had burned all my fuel...
We can burn a little more.
Okay.
We're gonna go to apoapsis now.
This actually got a little scary for a second.
Holy shit.
Okay, let's... let's just burn here and ha... be done with it!
Oh my god!
For some reason I was like, oh, we have infinite fuel, but that's not the case.
Woo!
Okay.
Let's go to 30.
Boom.
There we go.
That should be enough.
Where's Kerbin?
There it is.
We're gonna land on the lit side.
Whoa.
160...
Kilometers.
The big moment.
See ya, buddy.
Will our science...
survive the entry?
If we fuck this up, we're gonna lose Carson and Bob.
And they have some stars under their belt, okay?
Let's see if the actual...
mechanism will work.
Let's see if the test...
succeeded...
in proving that this is possible.
Okay.
Carson, Bob, game phase on.
We're gonna hold Retro on this.
I'm gonna start to heat now.
My question is, are my science experiments gonna survive?
I think at least this one will survive.
But then again, I mean, it is covered here on the sides, right?
So the plasma's gonna go around the vessel here and not actually touch it.
But...
I mean...
Who knows?
So far it looks pretty stable.
Battery's great.
We have actually not even run out of battery.
I mean...
It's out of my control.
Jesus, take the wheel.
Let's just enjoy the view.
What do they call this?
Like...
The two minutes of horror or something in real life when you actually...
You know, have the plasma around the vehicle.
You have like radio blackout and...
The people on the ground don't actually know whether or not they're making it.
Whether or not everything has gone to shit or they're okay.
You know, those two minutes or whatever, how long it is, is...
scary.
This game is like the definition of cinema.
Uh oh!
Why are you not holding retro?
I have to help!
It's like, uh...
The fly-by-wire system here is not actually precise.
Oh!
Uh oh!
No!
Oh my god!
I'm holding!
I'm holding the button!
It wants to tip over so bad!
Looks like we're stable though!
Holy shit!
The design is not fully...
I can't trust it.
I cannot trust it.
But this... this was okay.
Ohhhh!
We made it.
There's no way I can fuck up now.
As soon as I can do those...
Parachutes, I do them!
Beautiful.
Oh my god.
Scary stuff, huh?
We're gonna splash down or...
That looks like...
Grassland.
Or some kind of...
Greenery.
Oh yeah.
Nice.
Main chutes.
We're gonna have drogue deployment.
Right about now.
And look at us coming back with all the science!
Not bad.
In fact, I'm gonna be super greedy here.
And do science again when we land.
What is...
Look at that over there!
There's something red and white.
It's the Danish flag.
I don't know what it is.
What is that?
That looks like Stonehenge or something.
I'm actually so curious what...
I guess I could technically walk over there if I wanted to.
But I don't know if I want to.
You know?
Seems a little crazy.
Oh, we're tipping over.
Oh shit.
That's fine.
Should I exit though?
I mean, the entrance is here.
I could do it.
Rain cloud is coming.
Look at that.
What is that over there?
Can I see it from inside?
Oh, now I went outside.
No, fuck it.
Let's go back.
I don't care.
Too scary.
200 science!
130...
How many did I do?
Oh man, that's really good.
And let's not forget, I used a lot of money to upgrade...
this facility.
So we actually didn't have much money when we left here.
So we did earn a lot of money.
And we got science.
Next up, I think...
I mean, obviously we're gonna go to Minmus.
But should I grab something on the way?
Just a little something-something, you know?
Do we want any of this?
Ducted fan blade?
I mean...
No.
No!
No thanks.
I kinda wanna save my...
Science.
Yeah.
Yep!
We're saving it.
Until we have enough money where we can buy...
an upgrade for this so we can do the next stage here.
Cause this is gonna cost 160, look at that!
And which one do I take?
Weather analyzer?
Relay antenna.
Advanced electrics.
Photovoltaic panels.
Not retractable once deployed.
Okay, so they sort of expand.
Just like real ones.
In space.
I kinda want...
Like landing is like a big deal, you know?
So...
Maybe we go for...
Maybe I shouldn't look at this until I actually have the capability of getting it.
Um...
Take me to sunrise.
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, I thought...
No, nevermind.
Let's make another vessel!
Actually, it's gotta be like the same, almost.
Minimus Science vessel.
That went to...
The moon.
You know.
Whatever.
Now, do I wanna make modifications?
I think it was already perfect.
Carson and Bill...
Yeah.
How come Bill didn't level up from that?
Like, he was on the frickin' moon.
He was planting flags and playing golf on the moon.
I feel like that's a promotion in itself.
But okay.
Guess not.
Um...
Other than that...
The thing that really annoys me...
Is that the science junior is like this tiny part.
Like, I can't bring this with this rocket, you know?
I guess that's the trade-off.
If you wanna go bigger, you have to sacrifice some things.
But I guess you could put it inside this thing where you put it around it, you know?
Um...
Whatever that was called.
The payload thingy.
The Airstream Protective Shell.
Pomegranates.
Okay.
Uh, actually, I need to see if there's new missions.
Cause we're going to Minmus, so grabbing even more missions on the way could be amazing.
Position satellite in a specific orbit of Minmus!
We're constantly looking for how to make better use of satellites at Kerbal Motion LLC.
We wanna know what shades of green we'll see if we expose a Kerbal to high G-forces.
Now I need your help.
We need you to build a satellite to our specifications and deploy it into a very specific orbit around Minmus.
Wow.
Yeah, that is very specific.
Very specific- Wait.
That's gotta be like a great- Like, you can't expect me to be within the meter on that.
What the fuck?
Build a new unmanned probe that has an antenna and can generate power.
The probe must be fully assembled when launched.
Reach the designated orbit around Minmus within marginal deviation.
Have a thermometer on the satellite.
Maintain stability for 10 seconds.
Yo!
I wanna make satellites!
What the fuck?
That's a lot of money we're gonna get for this.
Wait.
Gather surface-deployed mystery goo observation signs from the surface- Oh, that's- We're doing that!
Definitely taking that.
Something about a satellite around Kerbin, too.
Yo, I'm actually intrigued by this.
I'm kind of intrigued.
But maybe we start with the normal Minmus mission and then we do this.
Sarah- Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is, by the way, why you wanna do these missions.
Did you remember how expensive it was to hire a Kerbal?
This is how to get them.
For free.
You know?
So maybe this is what we need to do a little bit of.
Just to have a backup...
Like, entourage of Kerbals.
Yeah, this one doesn't even pay that much.
I love this flag, though.
That's very cool-looking.
Big fan.
Pro-bo-bo-do-bo-dine.
Pro-bo-do-bo-dine.
Yeah.
That's such a weird name.
Kerbin World First's record-keeping society.
You've explored nearly every nook and cranny of Kerbin, but there are a few potentially profitable loose ends left to investigate.
Right, so this is...
They want me to dock.
Wait, docking on or around Kerbin?
Huh?
How...
How would you want me to dock on Kerbin?
Huh?
Dude, the complete...
It's like 5,000 we get for this.
It's nothing.
But I mean, I guess it's a good excuse to try and do the docking.
Because I do want to figure out how that works.
Maybe we do that, actually.
Yeah.
Let's try a docking...
thing.
In fact, how about this?
We can go up there and rescue somebody who's already in orbit.
Right?
And we have a little docking thingy on it.
Then we come up there with another vessel.
We dock with it.
And I guess then we have done the docking thing.
And then we undock.
But what is the point of them grabbing the guy?
I guess there's no point.
I mean, since we're going up there anyway, I guess.
Hmm.
Now for that...
Let me grab the...
crew.
Oh, but wait!
We can do this much better now!
We're going to make a...
God damn crew three!
Yeah, that's good.
Crew three is going to be...
Yeah, actually just get rid of all this.
I guess we're using this for that.
Easy peasy, lemon squeezy.
And then we do a...
quick and dirty heat shield.
Like that.
Don't need to do any signs here.
Parachute.
Two of these.
Wonderful.
Then we do a detachment thingy.
Too big.
There.
And then next up, next up, next up.
We do...
Just one of those, I would imagine.
Now wait, wait, wait.
So the docking thing.
The docking thing...
Where was that?
Coupling?
Okay, let's read this.
Originally marketed as a child-sized version of the normal Clamptron.
The Clamptron Jr. soon found use among hobbyists and professional space agencies alike.
For its compact, profile, lightweight structure.
And all-around cuteness.
As a result of its small size, kerbals need to hold their breath and wiggle to slip through.
Yeah, this didn't tell me anything.
This is a cargo part that can be placed inside inventories.
Wait, what?
What?
Really?
You put this in your pocket, huh?
Oh, wait a sec.
I guess I don't need to put it...
I guess I can do something like this.
Oh wait, why is it doing that?
Also, which way is the right way?
I feel like this looks more right to me.
Right?
That looks more correct.
You have the little hatches here.
But I guess you don't want to do it here anyway.
Unless you want to drown...
In kerosene.
Or whatever it is they're using in there.
You don't want to open this hatch, actually.
Right here.
This is a bad idea.
We need something else.
Maybe that?
Wait, so hold on.
Uh...
We bring this up and then...
Fucking hell.
Wait, it's tiny.
Wait a second.
Do we even need that?
Let me do this, dude.
Right?
And then this...
Like that.
I wonder though, like, can...
Kerbals go from this to that?
Hold on.
We gotta test something.
So Bill is in here now.
Oh, that's a lovely view.
Software glitch update before flight.
Don't forget!
Oh shit.
Okay.
Reminder, close the hatch.
And don't forget the snacks.
That's way too blurry.
It does not look like there's like a hatch you can...
Attach to it.
I am so confused.
Like how on earth does this work?
Let me actually see if I can find something about this.
Space travel?
Rocketry...
I have no idea.
Altimeter...
Construction gizmos.
No.
EVA activities.
Docking mode.
Right, I guess you wanna go into docking mode.
Does this guy have a docking thingy?
Is that a docking thingy there?
Dude!
I wanna make a fucking space station.
Oh my god.
And then...
Attach more and more.
Imagine...
Okay, this doesn't tell me anything it seems.
Uh...
Recover?
Let's just freaking get a thing up there with a little docking thingy on it.
And I guess if we don't plan on coming back...
Uh...
We don't need a parachute, right?
So...
Wait, why...
Why can't I click on this?
Oh.
That is so weird.
So we're gonna use this...
Wait, that almost looks like you can enter from here.
Maybe that is meant to be used with this actually.
Uh...
Utility?
Fuck, what was it?
Coupling...
Here.
Why won't it snap?
Oh.
That's almost too perfect, right?
It has to be the way it works.
Yeah, it doesn't...
Oh wait, it does wanna snap like that.
I think it's the other way.
Fuck, why am I so...
I'm so confused, like, which way it needs to go?
I...
I don't know.
I guess we'll find out.
Okay, so no parachutes on this guy, I guess.
And...
Let's add...
No.
I...
Oh god, I don't know, man.
I guess just a fuel tank on this.
Like that.
Add a tiny, tiny...
Fuel engine.
Oh wait a minute, if we wanna dock, we need, like, precision thrusting here.
We need RCS for this.
How about wait a sec.
Um...
Space station.
We're up there.
And we stay there.
Save.
I need to see something real quick.
How much science do I even have?
I think I have like 200.
Yeah!
Nice.
It was up here, wasn't it?
Propulsion systems.
Precision propulsion!
This is what I need.
External tank.
Wait, this is liquid fuel.
Separatron.
Monopropellant fuel engine.
Wait a second.
Didn't I already have some that I just didn't buy yet?
Here we go!
RCS.
Variable thruster block.
I guess I...
I mean...
It's so cheap.
Buy it all.
Advanced inline stabilizer.
Reaction wheels.
I guess this also consumes electricity.
0.5 per second.
Okay.
That's...
That's kind of a lot, actually, if you think about it.
Oh, dude!
If we're making space station, we're gonna have solar panels!
Oh, my God.
Uh...
I guess I just...
Whoa, that's tiny as hell.
What about this one?
A little bigger...
Why does it look like that?
Oh, that's more like it.
Look at that.
That's massive.
But I guess it's not variable.
I guess you wanna have...
Well, you would wanna have some on each end, at least.
Wait.
If you put...
I'm trying to think...
If you have two up top...
If you have two this way...
No, I guess, ideally, you would have four on each end.
For maximum control.
It's
like...
Oh, wait a minute.
What?
No, we don't need this, actually.
Because this is not the one I'm docking.
I'm coming up with another one that I need precision on.
This is just gonna stay there, right?
Yeah.
Actually, this is fine.
Okay.
So now, we do a decoupling sequence.
And we add...
Oh, this is gonna be an easy one, I guess.
We just add this.
That.
Let's make them white.
Little engine that could...
I like the swivel.
This is kinda funky, though.
Can you stop...
doing that?
God, why is it so finicky?
I mean...
Look at this rocket right here!
We already have a lot of Delta V.
What is it?
What?
Reset?
What'd I do?
Nothing to reset.
Okay.
I just panicked for no reason.
Bro, I feel like this is already a good enough rocket.
Am I crazy?
Basic fin.
That's a sexy rocket right here.
Am I missing anything?
So we bring up a guy.
Ah, but wait!
If we bring someone up, we ideally would wanna bring them back.
So let's try to do the thing where we...
where we bring in the computer.
But then I guess we don't need this.
Huh, wait.
Hold on.
Oh god.
Uh...
Was it up here?
Ah, you know what?
Let's just bring this guy up there that we don't care about.
Fuck Bill.
What about...
Honestly, I don't care about Bill.
Bill is gonna be up there.
He's the guy.
He's up there.
Just hanging out.
You know?
He's doing that.
That's cool.
Alright, Bill.
Next up, we're gonna have...
Uh...
I guess we don't need parachutes for this.
Oh man, I...
Do I really wanna bring the guy up there though?
Hmm...
Wait, I need to see something real quick.
There was something else I could buy?
Okay.
I do have 200 signs, right?
What was it?
Also, what is...
Spark?
Look at that thrust.
That is very tiny.
This is perfect for a space station!
Hitchhiker storage container!
I guess I...
Oh god.
Wait a minute.
Can I see like, docking things?
Docking...
Landing...
Over here...
Scanning...
Oh my god.
I mean...
Oh, I'm so overwhelmed, man.
Dude, I...
I need to try and understand how this works with the non-passenger thingy.
So like...
If I add this, right?
I can control it without a guy.
The problem is, I can't attach the docking thingy to it then.
And this one...
Is too tiny.
See?
So what the fuck?
Oh wait, unless, unless...
Wait...
Oh wait a minute.
You don't wanna...
Dock to a...
No, this makes no sense.
You wanna get inside, right?
That's the whole point of docking.
I have no idea.
Oh wait, I have an idea.
I have an idea.
Watch this.
We're gonna do...
Service bay.
Open it.
Whoops.
I'm gonna slam this guy in the center.
Oh!
It even snaps onto it!
That's more...
Oh, you know what else?
A space station needs science.
If we can fit it in there.
I guess we can fit these at least.
Oh, we can put them on the thing!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Uh...
Yes.
The goo thing is gonna be a little tight, I think.
Ah, we can actually kinda fit it here.
Or here.
Or there.
We can probably put it underneath and then...
Move it down slightly.
That feels bad.
We're not going...
I mean, we don't need goo in orbit anyway.
Let's be honest.
In fact, we don't need any of this in orbit.
Uh...
What we do need though...
Is...
Batteries.
And we can put that exactly where we had this...
Wait a second.
Oh my god.
Oh, that's perfect, dude!
This is 200 electric charge.
I'm gonna add even more.
Man, one on each side.
God, that's beautiful!
But, hold on.
We also need to, uh...
Have solar panels.
The question is, where do I put those?
I guess we can just sort of do this.
Hey, that works!
Or we put them directly on here too.
That also could be kinda cool.
Yo, that's super slick!
Oh my god.
Bill?
You're not going!
Although, I think Bill had a dream of going to the space station.
I guess we can bring someone up and...
And then we can experiment with trying to get people through, right?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, this is so cool.
Space station, uh...
I don't know, uh...
Space station.
What else?
Oh!
Wait!
Hold up!
A space station needs Science Junior!
Doesn't it?
And you know what else?
We're gonna add more solar panels.
Now that we have more surface area.
Oh my god.
So that way we have some on this direction and some over here.
All we need to worry about then is being, you know, on...
The right side of Kerbin.
Oh, this is looking glorious, bro.
Oh, man.
Dude!
Let's also bring an antenna!
Make it really science-y and shit.
Uh...
There.
Maybe back here.
Oh, we don't need two antennas.
Um...
One.
Then we extend it.
Oh my god, bro!
Come on!
Come on now!
That's sick!
Oi!
Oh!
Okay.
So we have 2,400 Delta V.
I wonder if that's enough to get to orbit.
Um...
Wait.
If I click on...
Wait, this one.
And I go...
So see, this is 1,578 at sea level.
That's pretty good.
This is 845 in...
No, that's...
Oh!
Okay, we have plenty.
Plenty!
This should be more than enough.
Which is kinda crazy because...
I had trouble getting to orbit early on.
And I'm pretty sure I made a rocket like this and I...
Couldn't even come close.
But okay, whatever.
What's the thrust to weight ratio on the first stage here?
Ooh!
Yikes!
I see the problem.
Ah, but wait!
I have a solution!
Oh my god!
Check this out!
Fuck the swivel.
We're gonna go reliant.
But then you're gonna go...
Oh!
But Oliver!
Then we don't have control!
But wait!
We do!
Advanced inline stabilizer.
We're gonna put this guy right here.
I mean, surely that will be enough.
Can we recolor that?
Reaction wheels normal?
Oh, wait, what?
Huh.
Okay.
I don't know what that means.
I mean, isn't it always SAS?
No, I guess if you try to turn it without SAS then...
Yeah.
Okay.
So what about now?
1.25!
That's...
Not bad.
Are you ready?
And we don't have any passengers.
Let's see if this works.
Fuck yeah.
Also, I gotta double check my staging.
I didn't check that before I left.
Yeah.
Looks good.
I have SAS?
We have no Kerbals on board!
I'm gonna turn...
Uh...
Oh, I definitely have control.
Look at this!
Let me see battery.
Oh, we got 460 battery, baby!
I'm gonna slightly...
Dude, I'm gonna master this...
Uh...
This first burn here at some point.
Okay, we're gonna start turning slightly.
For some reason my rocket wants to rotate all the time.
Every rocket I make wants to just rotate.
It wants to do a roll program.
Whatever.
I'm not gonna...
I'm not gonna fight it.
We are going very slow.
Let's not turn too much now.
It's kinda crazy I'm doing this without a Kerbal.
This is what we're...
What?
Oh God.
This is what we'll have to do when we start setting up rovers and stuff.
I think I turned too much too early, guys.
This is not...
That's way too much turnage.
I'm gonna hold it here for a bit.
Until we get more speed.
Wait.
Oh, we don't have enough...
Bro, what am I smoking here?
Oh no.
This design sucks!
I was misled by the numbers.
We're not even speeding up that much.
Oh God.
Apoapsis?
35?
Wait!
We don't even have a...
Oh, thank God we don't have any Kerbals on board.
Imagine we didn't have...
Dude!
We would have lost a Kerbal.
There's no way to abort.
It's...
It's orbit or nothing.
That's actually kinda scary when you think about it.
Wait, we actually have a bunch of fuel left.
So maybe it's okay.
Slightly turn this.
Apoapsis?
I wanna get that to at least 70.
Maybe a bit more.
Actually, I think we will have enough.
And remember, this engine gets more and more efficient the further up we are.
That's beautiful!
What a beautiful arc we got there.
Absolutely incredible.
Let's go to like 74...
Ish.
Five.
There we go.
And then...
Wait, I guess I can just do that here.
Right here.
How much do I need?
Whoa.
Now we're at...
218...
Uh-oh.
Does that mean I don't have enough?
Oh shit, what does that mean?
No, I must have enough.
Look at my shit.
Okay, you know, I don't trust this.
I don't trust the computer system.
Let's just burn.
Never tell me the odds.
TARS is wrong.
I am right.
Actually, I think I want to burn a little more like this.
Yeah, look, we definitely...
Look at this Delta V here.
Like, we have plenty?
This thing was lying to me.
Fucking asshole computer.
By the way, this is remote controlled right now.
This is so cool.
There's a Kerbal on...
Kerbin right now, sitting in a control room.
Doing this.
I'm not the one controlling this rocket.
Like, it's doing it on its own.
I haven't done anything since launch, by the way.
I've been acting like I did, but I haven't.
Okay, we should be like 2,300 meters per second.
For orbit here.
Maybe a bit less, even.
It's not perfect, because Apoapsis is going crazy.
And that makes me unhappy.
Oh, this is a horrible...
Situation.
Oh!
Ew!
Ow!
Burn like this now.
Please.
Please, for the love of God.
Get my Periapsis to 70, at least.
That's not gonna happen, is it?
You bastard!
Aw, fuck you.
It's fine.
I mean, I'll just go to Apoapsis and burn a little bit.
Let's go for a fully circular orbit, shall we?
What is my elevation?
I wish you could see that while in the map mode.
Oh, here we go.
There we go.
I need to slow down first, and then go up.
Cannot warp faster than 50x while below.
Okay, okay, got it.
Now we go over here.
It's gonna be quite a cool orbit.
Let's try and make it perfect.
Actually, let's try and do the calculation thing here.
Maneuver.
Uh, like this.
Wait, can I see the actual thing down there?
Periapsis.
I need to get that to 586.
56.
Oh, that's perfect.
585.
Oh, it's 590 now on that?
Why?
Oh,
wait.
Now I'm messing it up.
Ah, good enough.
Good enough.
Wait, did I have a contract for this?
Wait.
Attach two different vessels together near Kerbin with a docking port?
Or a claw?
The claw!
Okay.
So now we got a point here.
Okay, you know what?
I'm actually a fan of this maneuver mode here.
I was kind of hating on it at first, but now I think I love it.
13 second burn in five minutes.
Okay.
Beautiful.
Speed up.
Actually, I just click here.
So we burn at seven.
Let's say six and a half.
To be ultra mega precise here.
Here we go.
Actually, I just look at the burn time and stop when it's at zero.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Oh, it's not good enough though.
Is that an orbit or what?
Holy shit.
That is fricking fantastic.
Wow.
With no Kerbal!
So check it out.
What we're gonna do now...
We're gonna wait until this little guy right here...
Is somewhere over the space center.
Maybe like here.
Just so we give ourselves a bit of time.
Okay, shall we take a look then?
So
cool.
It even extended a little thingy in there.
What's battery looking like?
460?!
Transmit data...
God, I hope I actually...
Have this in the right order.
Like, um...
But this looks correct, doesn't it?
Like, the other one looked funky.
I can... I can do signs without Kerbal's.
Hey, we even get some signs!
Wow!
Wait, why is transmitting 0% signs value?
What?
Wait a second.
Why is that?
I wish there was a search option in this KSpedia.
Oh god.
Communications network?
ComNet?
Wait, KerbNet?
The current control path, as well as all potential links in the whole network, can be visualized in map view and the tracking station.
The panel shows relevant ComNet information including control level, signal strength, and destination type.
Last hop.
Wait, are we gonna be able to send like...
Oh shit.
We're gonna have multiple hops.
Meaning, we send signals from Kerban?
To like, I don't know, a vessel in orbit around...
Well, Mars or whatever, you know?
Like, whatever the equivalent is.
And then from that...
We send signals down to a rover.
You know what I mean?
Control links.
Crew...
Oh wait, crew plus probe.
Transmission.
With the correct equipment, a vessel can transmit its science data back to Kerban via ComNet.
The higher the signal strength, the more science results from the transmission.
Oh!
So, I guess I just need more antennas?
To actually get science from it?
It's always better to return the data than to transmit it, but a strong signal can make a lot of difference.
ComNet uses soft occlusion where signals are not cut off immediately when the destination goes over the horizon.
In addition, atmospheric bodies allow bouncing the signal through the atmosphere.
Furthering the distance below the horizon a destination can be?
That's crazy.
Damn.
Oh my god, look at this!
Different hops.
The signal strength is the product of the signal strength of all links on the path back to the DSN, or to a control point.
Ah, so you multiply the percentages.
Which are fractions, right?
So...
Relays?
Oh my god!
Yo!
Oh, this looks so cool!
This is exactly what I imagined!
I even imagined Mars!
Look at this, this looks like Mars!
I was thinking of rovers, you know?
Range?
What's Kirknet?
Woah, what?!
Okay, hold on, hold on.
I just got mega excited.
I'm not even gonna look at that.
I don't think I have access to that anyway right now.
Let's wait.
That sounds amazing.
Whatever I just saw there, whatever just entered my retina, made me excited.
Let me see this thing.
Oh, it even has a bit of electric charge on its...
Oh wait, Kirknet access.
Oh shit!
Never mind, I do have access to whatever this is.
Huh?
Oh!
What am I looking at?
Display mode.
Kirknet will automatically refresh every seven seconds?
But...
Okay, wait, wait.
Oh wait, am I...
Is that...
Is that what I'm seeing?
Wait, are we somehow recording what's on the planet right now?
How?
Divers passion?
What the fuck does that mean?
I don't understand.
We can check altitude...
Oh my god!
Placed waypoint divers passion on Kerbin at targeted location.
That's
crazy!
Oh wait, this is land?
This is...
No wait, what?
That doesn't make any sense.
Oh, maybe it's just like all...
This is all on land.
It's just...
This is like an altitude map.
Oh, altitude is minus?
No, this is below sea level then, right?
I'm assuming minus means below sea level.
So if I put it here...
Oh yeah, okay, okay!
Oh my god, this is fucking cool!
Wait, field of view!
Oh!
Jungle stupidity?
Wait, we get to figure out what these places are called on Kerbin.
Or what?
Refresh.
Can I remove these?
Delete.
Oh, this is so cool!
What are these quadrants?
So I guess the...
The little thing I have with me here...
Um, the Probodo Bodine Octo...
Is doing this...
Measurement?
This scan?
We can...
We can put it into hibernation.
What the...
This is amazing!
Carbonate access.
Unless it's using this somehow?
That's just an antenna.
I'm so confused...
Like, it's like it's automatically also aiming at the planet.
Oh my god, this is just the coolest...
Basically what I'm thinking now...
Is, if I can go to the moon with this...
And I can go like this...
Refresh...
And it will say...
Farsight Crater or something...
Then I know where it is!
I place a waypoint!
And I land!
And I get the moonstone!
Do you see what I mean?
This is groundbreaking.
If that is actually what this means.
Like, I don't know what jungle stupidity is...
And why is it everywhere?
You know?
Oh wait, no!
Cur...
Curbonaut's Nest.
So it's where I...
Waypoint.
Placed waypoint...
Just weird that it won't...
Huh.
Oh my god, this is so freaking good.
Oh my god, I'm so excited!
Curb net!
Alright!
Let's delete these.
Okay, anyway...
I just got distracted like crazy just now.
Um...
Let's go back...
To...
Uh...
Here...
We're gonna go to Space Center.
Cause it's time...
To dock!
Let's see here.
We're gonna make essentially the same thing.
With the exception of some...
Things.
Uh...
Don't want this.
Do want that, I think.
Do I want that?
Wait a second.
I guess...
Alright.
Then of course we need a...
Wait, do we?
Wait, what if I just send up another...
Uh...
Unmanned vehicle?
Nah, we gotta try and walk through the hatch, right?
Yeah.
We gotta try that.
Now of course, we will add parachutes, just in case...
Shit goes wrong.
So...
Let's do...
One of each.
Why is that one so big?
Oh my god.
It's a big boy.
Heat shield.
And...
Separator.
What the?
Haha.
No.
This is the guy we wanna be able to...
Fine maneuver.
So we definitely need to put on some...
RCS thrusters.
I'm gonna use four.
Here.
And then four.
There.
Wait a second.
Requires monopropellant.
This amount per second max.
Okay.
There's variance.
Oh.
Oh, that's cool.
Oh, you can even angle them like that.
Look.
But I guess, ideally, we...
Yeah, this is not...
This is not optimal.
This is optimal.
I guess.
But we need monopropellant then.
Monopropellant?
Okay.
I guess we buy that.
What else do I have that has that?
Uh...
No, this is solid fuel.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
How come I haven't tried these?
This looks unbelievable.
I may try these.
In the next rocket.
This is normal liquid fuel.
I think this is the only one I have.
So wait.
These are gonna use...
How much was it?
0.1 per second.
And...
This one has 20.
Oh.
Uh...
This is not very aerodynamic looking.
Also, I wonder...
Like, if I put them here...
Do these have access to them?
Or do I need to do a fuel transfer thingy?
Uh...
Hold on.
I'm gonna do a quick test.
Space station...
Docker.
Save...
Get rid of...
Wait a minute.
Yeah, get rid of this.
Yeah, fuck it.
We have money.
Uh...
The vessel has no remote control...
Oh.
Right.
But I guess we wanna bring a guy.
It's going to be...
Cargill.
I have deemed it so.
I need to test something real quick here.
RCS, I guess.
So it does work.
And look, it's being used.
Okay, confirmed.
Alright.
Recover.
There was something else I wanted to check, but I forgot what it was.
Okay.
Then we load the one I saved.
Space station...
Docker?
No!
I thought I saved it before I removed it, so it would...
I would still have it.
Ah, goddammit.
Wait, what did I even have now?
I forgot.
I guess it was a...
This one.
Then we put in...
That one.
Then we have...
These.
Let's bring a smaller one.
Gotta make it look nice.
And then down here...
I guess a swivel.
Let's see if it's enough.
1.11.
Let's add some solid stuff to this.
A simple, solid booster.
Never hurt anyone.
1.1.
But that's okay.
Whatever.
It's not amazing.
But it's okay.
So this one goes first.
Boom, boom.
They go together.
Separate.
Boom.
Here we wanna do...
This guy first.
And then that one.
In case we need to...
You know...
Abort the mission.
And then I guess the plan is...
We get up there.
We rendezvous.
And...
We somehow...
I guess we just have to make these touch or whatever.
We can go into docking mode or whatever.
And try that.
Yeah.
This, however, I'm not happy about.
I don't like the way this...
This looks very un...
Or not aerodynamic.
You know?
So we'll see how that actually goes.
Okay.
Carson.
Let's...
Do it.
Let's see if we can do this, man.
Just double check that we actually have the contract for the thingy.
Oh, I don't.
Oh, I do.
Dock two vessels on or around Kerbin.
Okay.
Wonderful.
You ready?
Three, two, one.
Boom!
Oh, that's very slow.
What the fuck?
Yo!
Yeah, the thrust to weight ratio is...
Terrible.
Absolutely terrible.
That's okay.
Carson...
I believe you can do it.
Carson, actually, let's see if you can beat a frickin' machine.
The machine did okay getting to orbit, but can you do better?
That's what I wanna know.
I do have a bit of control here.
It's not terrible.
Oh, shit.
Wow, it already ran out.
That was a terrible first stage.
I should have used the kickback instead.
Man, that was disappointing.
And I gotta be honest, the swivel is also kinda disappointing right now.
It's barely...
We may have to abort.
I'm not feeling good about this.
Carson, I'm sorry.
The engineers back at home have fucked it up.
What the hell was that?
Oh, I guess the stage exploded down below.
Only 260 meters per second right now.
Oh, man.
Let me look at this mode.
Only at 15k.
Okay.
Yeah, guys.
We may have to abort this.
I don't know.
I'm not feeling good.
Then again, we do have this stage up here, which has a lot of delta V.
The problem is, we're not very high up in the atmosphere right now, so when we start to burn that stage...
Not good.
Actually, maybe it's fine.
This is a weak engine.
It's almost like we didn't get any speed just now, but now we are.
It's gonna take a while.
Dude, we may not have enough to actually rendezvous.
We need a lot of fuel for that.
Let's have a look.
Especially because we are in a quite high orbit there.
Aww.
Are we cooked?
It smells bad.
Look at my stage.
It's getting very hard to read.
Space station...
Docker debris.
Okay, 70k.
Apoapsis.
I think we wait now.
Till we get up there.
Honestly, I think we should start burning already.
We shouldn't have stopped.
Because we need like...
1200 or so...
Delta V here.
It's gonna take a while.
The rocket looks cool.
Albeit a little...
weird.
But I dig it.
Half fuel left.
May have started to burn a little early.
I'm not sure.
Dude, I can do it.
I feel it.
We should be okay.
Okay.
And we also have RCS fuel, right?
Looks like Apoapsis is running away from me.
I don't like that.
1900.
And our fuel is...
It's not great.
I definitely burned a little too early.
Okay, get ready.
Periapsis is coming up.
And...
Right about...
No.
Wonderful.
Okay, so we are almost out of fuel.
And we have to rendezvous with this guy.
With the space station.
Shit.
Hmm.
Uh...
I guess we...
I guess we can use this.
Obviously, that's not gonna...
Wait, this is gonna be super easy.
I can just move this.
Need to think.
I guess my best bet...
Is to burn...
At some point where my Apoapsis just reaches...
You know, the elevation of the space station.
And then when we have the encounter...
Then we start to make the little adjustments to actually fly in formation.
Which basically means burning prograde, I guess.
But...
We gotta figure out when to do that.
And right now, we're kind of in a bad configuration.
I need to be behind him.
Something like this, maybe.
I think I'm a little too late.
No, actually, this is fine.
I'm gonna catch up to him.
I wonder if there's like a...
Systematic way of doing this.
Looks like we have a close encounter there.
Somewhat.
Sixteen kilometers.
Why is it, like, not closer?
Oh, the inclination is a little fucked.
We can add a bit of this.
Actually, I regret.
Twenty kilometers.
Twenty-five.
Thirty-five.
Dude, this is actually crazy.
Like, the fact that you can just do this.
I mean, I'll take that.
Twenty-six kilometers?
Oh man, there's so many lines.
I can barely see what's happening.
Yeah, we...
Oh, that's...
Yeah, we are too low.
That's simply what it is.
So that means...
Directly opposite.
We gotta do a little bit of this.
Why did that disappear?
Wait a sec.
No, no, no.
I need to burn here.
To raise the disc up there and down here.
I...
I messed it up.
Stop.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh, but I'm too late for that, I think.
Unless I'm not.
I have an idea.
We're gonna burn like this.
Right?
We're gonna get a close approach here.
As close as we can get.
Sixteen is good.
So we make this burn.
And then when we're over here, we start burning up.
Or normal.
That's the plan.
Great.
Okay, so...
Node in, uh...
Two minutes!
Beautiful.
So we aim along here.
On the nav ball.
We're in the darkness here.
So we burn at nine seconds.
Let's fast forward.
Let's not go too fast.
Get ready.
And go.
Actually, I look at this instead.
It's actually better.
Not bad.
And watch this now.
Now we go to...
The descending node.
Oh, is that the one telling me the difference in inclination?
Look, minus point eight.
I think that's the one.
I've been looking for that.
Jackie, no.
Oh, no.
Come here.
Okay.
You wanna see how I do rendezvous?
Look at this.
No.
Stay here, stay here.
You need to see how I do rendez...
Okay.
She doesn't wanna see how I do rendezvous.
That's fine.
He doesn't need to see that.
Oh, now we got way too far up.
Now it's 15 kilometers.
Can we bring it even closer?
18.
But I guess we can also just move this around like crazy.
Uh, have it there.
Uh, the problem is we're on an elliptical orbit, of course, so...
Burning normal at the descending node is gonna be weird now.
It's gonna result in some kind of...
Thing that I don't understand.
You know what I mean?
Let's just try and play around with this.
Be a little faster.
Hey, look at that!
8.5!
12...
I mean, I'll...
You know what?
I'll take that.
Maybe we bring it down just slightly as well.
14, that's bad.
8.5!
We're taking that.
So we gotta aim at...
The blue one.
Let me see battery.
Wait, we don't actually have a lot of battery!
We gotta be careful.
Why didn't I bring a battery pack?
We...
We burned for one second?
In seven minutes.
This is a very slight adjustment.
Get ready.
It's gonna be a...
I'm gonna click and then de-click immediately.
It's gonna be fast.
Here we go, here we go.
Ooh, not bad!
9.4.
Okay.
Now we wait.
Oh, the space station, I'm coming for you!
I'm on my way.
I'm gonna be at a bit of a higher orbit here, which makes us slower so we can catch up.
Until it's perfectly calculated and we are very close.
Now I need to start targeting my target, which is...
The space station.
How's battery?
Doing good.
Here we go.
Get ready.
There you are!
Obviously we wanna...
Wait, you're moving closer to me.
Wait, shit.
Oh god.
Dude, we gotta start slowing down.
Holy shit!
We're coming in way too hot!
Way too hot!
Oh my god!
Oh crap!
We're at three!
Oh my god!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I'm fucking up, I'm fucking up!
I don't know what I'm doing.
We don't have infinite fuel.
Shit!
Bye-bye.
Wait, what do I do now?
Uh...
Switch vessel!
Map.
We have fuel on this guy.
Oh god.
Is that his target?
There you are.
We don't have a lot of fuel though.
Okay.
Okay, now we're moving towards each other.
Orbit looks good.
Yes.
Speed up a bit.
We don't have a lot of fuel here.
We have 300 delta V.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Slow down a bit.
Now we turn around.
Getting closer.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Man, the...
The frickin' machine here is doing work.
Getting closer.
There it is!
Okay.
Switch.
Now, how the hell?
Are we gonna do this?
Also, wait a minute.
I'm gonna have to...
I'm gonna turn this around.
So we're phasing.
There.
And switch.
Now.
Now to figure out how this works.
Obviously, we gotta try the docking mode.
RCS?
How the hell is this working?
Oh shit.
We're already moving away from...
Fuck.
Wait, hold on.
I need to get my cheat sheet.
There was something about RCS keybinds.
I gotta get that out.
Cheat sheet.
Keybinds.
There we go.
Hold on.
This one.
That one.
Okay.
Okay, so it says...
Flight.
Toggle RCS.
Forward, backward.
H and N.
RCS.
Left, right.
J, L and I, K.
What the fuck?
What do you mean?
Wait, what did it say?
Forward, backward is H and N.
But I don't want to do that just now.
I kind of just want to rotate.
And if I do...
Oh fuck.
Dude, I have no idea how this works!
What about I and K?
I'm so confused.
Also, what is this even...
Oh wait, now it's different.
There we go.
And now...
Wait, we're moving...
Towards.
Towards, okay.
But we're...
Oh wait, our vector is here.
Oh, this is awkward.
Wait, what the...
I'm so confused.
So wait, uh...
Forward, back...
H and N.
Oh, okay, I see, I see.
And...
RCS...
Left...
J-L-I-K...
Wait, how does that make sense?
It's J-L...
Oh, oh, it's like W-A-S-D!
So up, down...
Uh...
Wait, we want to do forward.
So that is...
Forward...
H.
Okay.
Oh, I see!
So H, and then we do...
Can I do precision...
On this...
Caps lock?
Oh, you definitely can!
Oh, we're actually moving towards it.
Also, I need to...
Move my...
Ball right on it.
Like there.
Okay, and now...
So H, N...
Move it up.
It's inverted!
We're moving closer!
And I'm not gonna change...
We have 0.6 right now.
I'm gonna leave it at that.
And then we're gonna slow...
So that's N when we get close.
I'm gonna speed up a little bit, because I'm a...
Crazy bastard.
Holy shit.
Oh my god!
We're perfectly aligned, dude!
No, we're not.
We're not.
We're coming in at an angle, kinda.
Are we not coming in...
At an angle?
Looks like an angle to me.
Hohoho!
Oh my god, it sucked it in!
Magnus!
Wow!
Dude, that's fucking cool!
Dock 2 vessels on, or...
Okay, so now I wonder...
How do I then transfer my guy?
Transfer crew?
Oh my god!
That is so cool!
Wow!
But what about...
What about the docking mode?
I don't understand this.
Like, when I was in docking mode, like, the keybinds didn't do anything that made sense at all.
It was so weird.
And then when I exited docking mode, it made sense.
So...
I don't know.
No idea.
Undock.
Ooh...
I guess...
What, hold on.
No, you know what?
I guess Carson can stay up here.
For a bit.
Oh wait, so wait.
Are we actually one vessel now, or what?
How does this work?
Transfer crew.
Command.
Oh, control from here.
Wait, which one...
This one has fuel.
Oh, Jackie, come here.
Come here, Jackie.
Oh, you want food, of course.
Yeah, I'm gonna stop in a second here.
What's up, Jackie?
Did you see I docked the vessel?
Look.
They're in a stable orbit.
It's a space station.
I love you.
Okay.
Space center.
That was beautiful.
That was absolutely amazing.
Let's warp to sunrise.
And we're gonna call it a day.
I actually have a bit of a headache right now, for some reason.
My head is hurting!
Alright, people.
I need to take a...
sip of my drink here.
I think that's why I'm having a headache.
I haven't even been touching my drink.
I didn't follow the hydration rule.
So what did you think of that ending there?
Wasn't that an amazing ending?
Great job not killing any Kerbals today.
Thank you.
Wait, did I not kill any?
I guess I didn't.
That was so good.
We discovered so many new things.
I also...
Dude, I was...
I think one of the reasons I have a headache...
Like, I was so overwhelmed by all the new parts.
Like, you right click a new part, and it has like 10 other options, you know?
Our ending for now, not the game.
Just the stream.
NASA uses RCS to deorbit?
Yeah, it makes sense.
You don't need a lot of Delta V to deorbit.
Epic Minimus landing, by the way?
Thank you.
That was good.
Please send Carson back home.
He misses his family.
Nah.
I mean...
Listen.
Real astronauts stay on the space station for years, you know?
Actually, I don't know what the record is right now.
Is it one year or something?
It's definitely more than one year.
He can afford to stay up there for a bit.
They're snacks.
And he can communicate with his family via the antenna.
It's a high-gain antenna.
It's okay.
Did you know he can pan the camera with middle mouse?
I actually did know, but I forgot to do it today.
I figured that out last time.
I completely forgot about it.
But yeah, next time I'll try it.
Please send more snacks.
What kind of snacks do you like?
What are you guys' favorite snacks?
I'm kind of a, you know, sour candy guy.
Or cheesecake.
That's, like, amazing, too.
Oreo and popcorn.
Those are good ones.
I'm not a big fan of nougat.
A lot of people eat that for Christmas and I hate it.
Jomama.
Oh yeah?
I've been snacking on Jomama.
Skittles.
I like Skittles.
I prefer the sour ones.
Anything that kills my teeth.
I mean...
I agree.
I think I'm a little addicted to sugar right now.
Like, I get this sort of craving, you know?
Especially in the evening.
Like, damn.
It's almost like I can't think or do anything unless I have, like, a tiny bag of candy.
So I think that's the sign of an addiction.
And as soon as I have that bag, it's like I can relax.
You know what I mean?
So I always end up going to the store at, like...
Like a second trip, you know?
Really late.
Right before it closes.
And I always sit at home debating whether or not I really should go there and grab this bag.
And it's so tough.
So tough, man.
Is croissant a snack?
I would say it could be, yeah.
It's bulking season.
I have never actually worked out, like, for real.
I've had, like, a couple months where I did it, but I never could maintain it.
I hate it.
It's so boring.
It's the worst.
You had some cheesecake while watching?
I'm so jealous!
I can't find any cheesecake anywhere here.
I've been to, like, four different supermarkets lately.
I can't find it.
Have you tried java cakes?
Wait, is that a reference to Star Wars?
Or is that a real one?
Wait, I think I'm thinking of Jabba the Hutt right now.
I don't think it's related.
Never mind.
I have not tried java cakes.
Did you try Chatterer mod?
Oh, I actually forgot.
It sounds awesome.
I'm gonna try it.
Chatterer.
Someone recommended it last time.
I did actually want to try it out, but I forgot.
Chatterer and better time warp.
What is better time warp?
Like, how- what do you mean better?
What does it do?
Faster time warp and fixes bugs.
Oh, really?
Is it not gonna introduce any bugs, though?
I feel like when you mess with the physics stuff, when you fast forward, things can go wrong, right?
And if a mod tries to mess with that, I don't know.
Is it really good?
No, uh, the powder-topian.
Apparently I don't need planet shine, because it's part of whatever mods I have right now.
And that's coming from the creator of the cloud mods.
Chatterer is just annoying.
I mean, I'll check it out, see what it is.
See how it feels.
You know?
Yeah, so it's like they have, like, real conversations from astronauts, and they have, like, I guess pitched them up or something to make them sound like Kerbals.
And then they appear randomly or whatever.
It sounds pretty cool, but it could easily be annoying, I guess.
We'll see.
What was the new thing you weren't gonna react to?
Wait, what?
Oh, it was the smoke, of course!
The smoke from the solid rocket booster.
And I told you it would be obvious, right?
Sounds are pretty low-quality in KSP.
Maybe there's a mod for those.
Wait, which sounds are you talking about?
Will you update your mod list in the VOD's details?
I do that every time.
If you notice, uh, under each video, I have it changed every time.
So whatever is on that list is what is happening in that VOD.
So, for example, in, I think, the second stream, I used, uh, set theme.
And that is not- that is also in the mod list under that VOD, you know?
Yeah, I'm using the volumetric clouds mod.
We have a hairstyle mod.
Guys, I'm- I'm gonna go- I have a headache.
I have a crazy headache right now for some reason.
As soon as I looked away from the monitor, it really started pumping in my head for some reason.
But, this was a good stream.
We landed on Minmus.
We- uh, what else did we do?
We- we docked two vessels.
Which was amazing.
We have the start of a space station going on right now.
But I guess you have to kinda- Wait, how do I even- I guess I can't attach more.
Unless I de-attach and then attach something else that has another attach point.
Oh my god, this is getting weird.
Anyway, thanks for watching.
I'll see you around.
Enjoy your weekend, okay?
Bye-bye.